Ready?
準備？
Welcome to the second part of the program.
プログラムの第 2 部へようこそ。
The second part of the program is about the knowledge of the second month.
プログラムの後半は、2 か月目の知識についてです。
Let's start.
はじめましょう。
Please welcome the vice president of the Wang Hui Jun.
王輝軍副総統を歓迎します。
Thank you for your time.
お時間をいただきありがとうございます。
Good evening, everyone.
皆さん、こんばんわ。
Thank you for joining us today.
本日はご参加いただきありがとうございました。
Thank you for your time.
お時間をいただきありがとうございます。
Today we are very happy to invite you to the Institute of Biochemistry, Academia Sinica
本日は、皆さんを中央研究院生化学研究所にご招待できることを大変うれしく思います。
Professor Lin Junhong, Researcher of the Institute of Biochemistry
リン・ジュンホン教授、生化学研究所研究員
Let me introduce Professor Lin a little bit, although you may have one
リン先生をお持ちかも知れませんが、少し紹介させてください。
However, there is a bit of information on this that is not quite correct.
ただし、これに関しては完全に正しくない情報が少しあります。
That Professor Lin Junhong graduated from the Chemistry Department of our National Taiwan University
あの林俊宏教授は私たちの国立台湾大学化学科を卒業しました
So is it my junior brother or someone called me just now?
それで、それは私の後輩ですか、それとも今誰かが私に電話をかけてきたのですか？
What is it called Tang? Brother Tang, some people say that I am Tang Gong or something
それは唐と呼ばれていますか? 唐兄弟、私を唐公か何かだと言う人もいます。
anyway, so I'm a grown-up
とにかく大人になったので
After he graduated from the Chemistry Department of National Taiwan University in 1990,
その後、1990年に国立台湾大学化学科を卒業。
Just go to the Scripps Research Institute in the United States
アメリカのスクリップス研究所に行ってください
It was a very distinguished
とても格別なものでした
the research unit
この研究ユニット
academic unit
学術単位
you may
してもいいです
Some are not clear, but if I say that Dean Weng used to work there
いくつかは明らかではありませんが、ディーン・ウェンがかつてそこで働いていたと言えば、
in the back
後ろに
Before our middle school
私たちの中学校に入る前に
When he was dean he was in
彼が学部長だったとき、彼はそこにいた
Scripps
スクリップス
Our teacher Lin Junhong is here
私たちの先生、リン・ジュンホンが来ました
Under the guidance of Dean Weng
ディーン・ウェン氏の指導のもと、
received this Ph.D.
この博士号を取得しました
then
それから
Arrived on the east coast of Harvard in the United States
アメリカのハーバード大学東海岸に到着
From West Coast to East Coast Harvard University
西海岸から東海岸へ ハーバード大学
of this
これの
It's a medical school
医学部ですよ
This one is very famous with Chris Walsh
これはクリス・ウォルシュで非常に有名です
this
これ
The professor is also doing a very good job in developing drugs
教授は薬の開発でも非常に良い仕事をしています
so we are
だから私たちは
There is a saying in academia that says
学界にはこんな格言がある
his portal is very good
彼のポータルはとても良いです
The Right Pedigree
正しい血統
after that come back
その後戻ってきてください
quilt
キルト
At that time, the director of our mythology
あの時、僕らの神話の監督は
Director Liu Derong
監督 リウ・デロン
Recruit back
再び採用する
Since then, he has performed very well.
復帰後、彼はとても良いパフォーマンスを見せた。
that's a lot
それは多いです
many awards
多くの賞を受賞
then this
それからこれ
Here, for example, in
ここでは、たとえば、
Scripts already got a lot
スクリプトにはすでにたくさんのものがあります
nice award
素敵な賞
The trustee then transmits the academic award
その後、理事は学術賞を送信します
This is not easy
これは簡単ではありません
Because you are applying for this award in Taiwan
台湾でこの賞に応募しているため
It seems that our comprehensive hospital only gets one
うちの総合病院では1件しかもらえないみたいです
so he got the award too
それで彼も賞を受賞しました
so recently
とても最近
He also got our Li Tiande
彼は私たちの李天徳も手に入れました
he is a drug company
彼は製薬会社です
He has an established some young academic awards
彼は若い学術賞をいくつか確立している
he also got the award
彼も賞を受賞した
Also very famous internationally
海外でも非常に有名です
He also got us a
彼はまた私たちに
An Academic Alliance of Developing Countries
発展途上国の学術同盟
We are Pros
私たちはプロです
he also got the young man award
彼は若手賞も受賞した
So it's all young young young
だからそれはすべて若い、若い、若い
so he's our ten youngest
だから彼は私たちの10番目の末っ子です
what is it call
何と呼んでいますか
top ten potential figures
上位 10 位の潜在的な人物
So it's not just potential
つまり、単なる可能性ではないのです
he is doing very well now
他現在表現非常好
So the potential has been fully realized
ポテンシャルが十分に発揮されているので、
so we are very happy to have this opportunity
この機会をいただけてとても嬉しいです
This information says
この情報によると、
it's an associate researcher at the manager center
マネージャーセンターの准研究員です
That's wrong, now a researcher
それは違います、今は研究者です
National Taiwan University is also a professor, not an associate professor
国立台湾大学も准教授ではなく教授です。
So this data
それでこのデータは
I'm going back to this
これに戻ります
Was it made by the secretary team?
秘書チームが作ったのですか？
I'm going to integer integer
整数を整数にします
How to use old data to share with others
古いデータを使用して他の人と共有する方法
Excuse me
すみません
But today he's going to make us a
でも今日、彼は私たちを
I believe sir is a brilliant actor
先生は素晴らしい俳優だと思います
called health medicine tonic
健康薬強壮剤と呼ばれる
I now think he was super wrong
今思うと彼は非常に間違っていたと思う
is the name of the movie
映画の名前です
But he's coming to tell us in a simple way
でも彼はシンプルな方法で私たちに伝えに来ます
Come talk to us about drug development
創薬についてぜひご相談ください
what's the matter with this aspect
この面はどうしたのですか
have some secrets
いくつかの秘密があります
So he's coming to make a
それで彼は何かを作りに来ています
It's an in-depth introduction
詳しい紹介です
Today's Liberty Times
今日のリバティタイムズ
In fact, his secret has been leaked
実は彼の秘密が漏れてしまった
So I wrote a little report in it
そこでちょっとしたレポートを書きました
Then we warmly welcome Professor Lin
それでは、リン教授を心より歓迎いたします。
Thank you Vice President Wang
王副社長に感謝します
can you hear my voice
私の声が聞こえますか
First time using this microphone
このマイクを初めて使用する
they say i look like mike jackson
彼らは私がマイク・ジャクソンに似ていると言います
But I'm not that handsome
でも私はそんなにハンサムではない
skin is not so white
肌はそんなに白くない
First of all, I am very grateful to Vice President Wang for the opportunity
まず最初に、機会を与えてくださった王副社長に非常に感謝しています。
Vice President Wang was actually the head of the house who was on us before.
王副総統は、実は以前私たちと一緒にいた家長でした。
He actually promoted me
彼は実際に私を昇進させました
Today I am also very grateful to Wang for the opportunity
今日も機会を与えてくださった王氏にとても感謝しています。
Because I am doing drug development
創薬をやっているので
I usually collect some information
普段から色々な情報を集めているのですが、
So when the secretary group informed me that
それで、秘書グループから私にその旨の連絡があったとき、
When you have this please let me talk about this aspect
これを手に入れたら、この点について話させてください
Actually I was shocked
実はショックでした
Because I see the presentation time is about 90 minutes
発表時間が90分くらいあるみたいなので
usually i give speeches outside
普段は外でスピーチをします
I only have 40 minutes for my major
専攻の時間は 40 分しかありません
Suddenly it's 90 minutes
あっという間に90分になった
It's a bit of a mess
ちょっと混乱しています
So or I still collect some data
それで、または私はまだいくつかのデータを収集しています
let everyone share
みんなで共有しましょう
So what am I going to talk about today?
それで今日は何について話しましょうか？
what about first
最初はどうですか
Everyone seems to have a lot of this drug
みんなこの薬をたくさん持っているようです
But I put this drug into a large category
しかし私はこの薬を大きなカテゴリーに入れます
first category
最初のカテゴリー
This drug is very likely to have something to do with our life-threatening
この薬は私たちの生命を脅かす問題に関係している可能性が非常に高いです
For example, when you are infected with bacteria inside
例えば体内に細菌が感染した場合
You may soon be off antibiotics
もうすぐ抗生物質をやめられるかもしれません
that or
それか
For example, if you encounter cancer
たとえば、がんに罹患した場合
How do we take an anticancer drug like this
このような抗がん剤の服用方法
This is life threatening
これは生命を脅かすものです
The second category is related to our quality of life
2 番目のカテゴリーは生活の質に関係します。
Say you gain weight
太ったと言う
then i think you are no threat to your life
それなら、あなたはあなたの命を脅かすものではないと思います
Of course we want to be thinner
もちろん痩せたいです
so let me tell you
それで教えてあげましょう
about diet pills
ダイエット薬について
Well of course the Will cylinder
もちろんウィルシリンダーです
words for boys
男の子への言葉
Of course it is a serious disease
もちろん重篤な病気です
That's Will Cylinder
それがウィルシリンダーです
That is to say, you may need to know that normal
つまり、通常のことを知る必要があるかもしれません。
like our joints
私たちの関節のように
If you want to strengthen joint function, there is Hanan
関節機能を強化したいならハナン
or girls
または女の子
In our general cosmetics
弊社の一般化粧品では
added uric acid
尿酸を加えた
I will introduce you
ご紹介します
The third category is related to our daily life
3 番目のカテゴリーは日常生活に関連したものです。
related drugs
関連薬
For example, in our life
たとえば、私たちの生活の中で、
south americans have some ailments
南米人はいくつかの病気を抱えている
how to take painkillers
鎮痛剤の飲み方
like aspirin or these
アスピリンやこれらのような
Proton these drugs
プロトンこれらの薬
In the end, I will talk about two meanings
最後に二つの意味を言います
one is
一つは
Thalidomide
サリドマイド
this is in
これは入っています
in the 50s and 6s
50年代と6年代に
famous drug
有名な薬
then it had a pretty tragic outcome
その後、かなり悲劇的な結果になりました
You may also
また、
It's what we usually see in newspapers now
今ではよく新聞で見かける光景です
academic unit
学術単位
Including our Academia Sinica or other universities
私たちの中央研究院または他の大学を含む
There is often a press release of some research and development results
研究開発成果のプレスリリースが頻繁にあります。
often talk about
よく話します
Such research and development results
このような研究開発成果
may say expected
予想通りと言えるかもしれない
Maybe for example it will go into the development of a drug
おそらく、それは医薬品の開発に関わることになるでしょう。
May be available in 10 years
10年以内には入手可能になるかもしれない
What the hell are these press releases?
このプレスリリースは一体何なのでしょうか？
Of course it's a press release written by a reporter
もちろん記者が書いたプレスリリースです
that may not be entirely true
それは完全に真実ではないかもしれません
But it's in every press release
でもそれはどのプレスリリースにも書いてある
it told you
それはあなたに言いました
It is said to be related to drug development
創薬に関係があると言われています
what does that mean
どういう意味ですか
then i think last
それから私は最後に思います
Then I will give you some very simple introductions
それでは、とても簡単な紹介をさせていただきます
But at the very beginning, let me tell you something
でも、最初に言っておきますが、
that is
あれは
this way
こちらです
This is a prescription, it's my family's prescription.
これは処方箋です、私の家族の処方箋です。
I'm sorry because this isn't obvious by itself.
これだけでは明らかではないので申し訳ありません。
But generally speaking, if you say that in your daily life
でも、一般的に言えば、日常生活でそれを言うなら、
you
あなた
Get a prescription first, for example, recently everyone
まずは処方箋をもらってください、例えば最近皆さん
cold
寒い
Then of course you go back to the clinic to get some medicine
それからもちろん、薬をもらいにクリニックに戻ります
After taking the medicine, you are
薬を服用した後は、
Just obediently listen to the doctor's instructions
医師の指示は素直に聞いてください
The instructions say to eat several times a day or eat raw liver
説明書には、1日に数回食べるか、生のレバーを食べるようにと書かれています。
or anti eat
またはアンチイート
Did you take a closer look at your
あなたのことをもっと詳しく見ましたか？
What's in it?
何が入ってるの？
Then I will give a speech today, of course
それなら今日はもちろんスピーチします
I though
でも、
but impossible
でも無理
I am not a doctor myself
私自身は医師ではありません
I won't tell you what medicine you should and should not take
どの薬を服用すべきか、どの薬を服用してはいけないかは教えません
You guys can't have listened to me for 90 minutes
90分も私の話を聞くことはできなかったでしょう
You know what medicine to take when you give a speech
スピーチをするときにどんな薬を飲めばいいのか知っていますか？
But I want you to be able to say
でも言えるようにしてほしい
In the future, in your daily life, for example, if you see the drug list
将来、例えば日常生活の中で医薬品リストを見たら
At least I will care about the medicines you take
少なくとも私はあなたが服用している薬には気を配ります
what ingredients
どのような成分が
Now that the Internet is developed
インターネットが発達した今では
In the past you might have to look up books
昔は本を調べなければならなかったかもしれない
Now you just look it up online
あとはネットで調べるだけです
probably in
おそらく中に
You'll know the answer in a minute or two
1 ～ 2 分以内に答えがわかります
There are two medicines here
ここに薬が2つあります
i want to tell you
私はあなたに伝えたいです
One is keratomysine
一つはケラトミシンです
This is when my family member catches a cold
家族が風邪を引いたときです
Medicines taken at the clinic
クリニックでもらった薬
keratomysine is an antibiotic
ケラトミシンは抗生物質です
Then the other semitidine is stomach medicine
それからもう一つのセミチジンは胃薬です
That probably means that the medicine contains
ということはおそらくその薬には以下の成分が含まれているということでしょう
it has some stomach irritating ingredients
胃を刺激する成分が含まれています
So the doctor prescribed a semitidine
そこで医師はセミチジンを処方しました
it is a stomach medicine
それは胃薬です
gastric protection
胃の保護
The other three or four ingredients
残りの3つまたは4つの材料
is a component of Violet
バイオレットの成分です
So let's get into the topic now
それでは、今から本題に入りましょう
the first topic is antibiotics
最初の話題は抗生物質についてです
But in this part
しかしこの部分では
maybe say sorry
たぶんごめんなさいと言う
Because of many drugs
たくさんの薬のせいで
In fact, there are many complicated pharmacology involved in it.
実際、それには多くの複雑な薬理学が関係しています。
that many some nouns
その多くのいくつかの名詞
what about these nouns
これらの名詞はどうですか
It's really hard for me to translate it one by one
一つ一つ訳すのは本当に大変です
and many many English
そしてたくさんの英語
But of course I try to use
でももちろん使ってみます
Let me introduce you in a way
ある意味紹介させてください
First of all, the first topic I want to talk about today is related to antibiotics.
まず、今日お話ししたい第一のテーマは、抗生物質に関するものです。
What are antibiotics?
抗生物質とは何ですか?
Basically it's for bacterial infections when
基本的には細菌感染症の場合です。
antibacterial
抗生素殺菌的
Of course, if you have a little
もちろん、少しでもあれば
That is to say, if there is a little bit about this aspect
つまり、この点について少しでもあれば
The first antibiotic was penicillin
最初の抗生物質はペニシリンでした
what about this topic
この話題はどうですか
I might give you an introduction
ご紹介させていただくかも知れません
who was the first inventor
最初の発明者は誰でしたか
The first antibiotic was penicillin
最初の抗生物質はペニシリンでした
who is the inventor
発明者は誰ですか
where does it work
どこで機能しますか
Because the bacteria we have today have invaded the human body
なぜなら、私たちが今いる細菌が人体に侵入したからです。
Then our medicine must be selective, of course.
そうなると、当然のことながら、私たちの医療は選択的でなければなりません。
because our medicine
なぜなら私たちの薬は
actually a chemical
実は化学物質
if you eat it
それを食べたら
what about the drug
薬はどうですか
hope it doesn't affect anyone
誰にも影響が及ばないことを祈ります
have an effect on bacteria
細菌に影響を与える
So let me tell you about this later
ということで、これについては後ほどお話しましょう
How does it work?
どのように機能するのでしょうか?
It is related to the cell B of the bacteria
細菌の細胞Bに関係しています
why wait a minute
なぜちょっと待ってください
how did it find out
どうやってわかったのですか
it's an interesting process
それは興味深いプロセスです
i will explain
説明します
And because when it was discovered
そしてそれが発見されたときから
The timing of this discovery was at
この発見のタイミングは、
Before the Second World Mass in 1928
1928 年の第 2 回世界ミサ前
Then its research and development from the discovery
そして発見からその研究開発へ
be mass-produced in the end
最終的には量産される
applied to human medicine
人間の医療に応用される
In fact, it's time for the second mass
実はもう２回目のミサの時間です
so what
だから何
In fact many people say
実際に多くの人がこう言います
What about an invention like this?
こんな発明はどうでしょうか？
Actually changed the secondary world a lot
実は二次世界を大きく変えた
final result
最終結果
why wait a minute
なぜちょっと待ってください
After the mass of the second world
第二世界のミサの後
after
後
Because of this success
この成功のおかげで
So many pharmaceutical companies started
非常に多くの製薬会社が設立されました
started some searching
いくつかの検索を開始しました
Are there other drug molecules
他の薬物分子はありますか
that also has a bactericidal effect
殺菌効果もあるので
And so began a chain of discoveries that began
こうして発見の連鎖が始まりました
And while there are many, many drugs
そして、非常に多くの薬がありますが、
with antibiotics
抗生物質を使った
are antibiotics are antibiotics
抗生物質です 抗生物質です
But what?
でも何？
as a result of our abuse
私たちの虐待の結果として
Or the bacteria themselves are constantly de-evolving
あるいは細菌自体が常に進化し続けている
or there are constantly some strategies coming out
あるいは常にいくつかの戦略が出てきます
So now we meet
それで今私たちは会います
The biggest problem is a problem of drug resistance
最大の問題は薬剤耐性の問題です
Protect the most points
保護最分
On the topic of public security, I will use these projects to give you an introduction
公安のテーマについて、これらのプロジェクトを使用して紹介します。
before that
それ以前は
Let me tell you about the medicine in Huang'an
黄安の薬についてお話しましょう
Because of the medicine in Huang'an
黄安の薬のせいで
In fact, before the invention of adenoids
実は、アデノイドが発明される前は、
That
それか
before discovery antibiotic
抗生物質が発見される前に
A drug just before aventin was invented
アベンチンが発明される直前の薬
What about Huang'an's medicine?
黄安の薬はどうですか？
By itself we say that he is a drug of resistin
それ自体で彼はレジスチンの薬であると言います
Why didn't we say he wasn't a resistin?
なぜ彼はレジスタンスではないと言わなかったのでしょうか？
Because Huangan's medicine now knows that he is
黄安の医学は彼がそうであることを知っているからです
the growth of a fine smoke
一次細菸的生長
so when you
だからあなたが
When the liver is infected with small fine tobacco, you use Huang'an medicine
肝臓が小さな細かいタバコに感染した場合、黄安薬を使用します
That's Huang'an medicine?
黄安薬ですか？
In fact, it can temporarily prevent the growth of thin smoke so fast
実際、薄い煙が急速に成長するのを一時的に防ぐことができます。
because if everyone knows
なぜなら誰もが知っていれば
If the growth of thin smoke is based on Daanmen
薄い煙の成長が大安門に基づいている場合
Is after 20 minutes a generation can start reinstatement
20 分後に世代が復元を開始できるようになります
20 minutes grows very fast
20分はあっという間に過ぎてしまいます
So if you take Huang'an medicine
それで黄安薬を飲むと
In fact he's mainly targeting his folic acid synthesis
実際、彼は主に葉酸合成をターゲットにしている
Growth of folic acid into pholate
葉酸からリン酸塩への成長
What about Huang'an's medicine?
黄安の薬はどうですか？
So he is because of the ability to block fine smoke
つまり、彼は細かい煙を遮断する能力があるためです
So bacteria because they need folic acid nutrients
バクテリアは葉酸の栄養素を必要とするので、
so it will grow suppressed
だから抑制されて成長するだろう
At this time, if your immune system is strong enough
この時点で免疫力が十分に強ければ
If bacteria grow repressed
細菌の増殖が抑制されると
If your immune system is strong enough to handle it
免疫システムがそれに対処できるほど十分に強い場合
Then your bacterial infection can of course be cured
そうすれば細菌感染ももちろん治ります
So what about the internal medicine? It's not an antibiotic.
では内服薬はどうでしょうかというと、抗生物質ではありません。
Because it is, it can only be said that it is a drug that can resist vitamins
ですので、ビタミンに強い薬としか言えません。
But before the invention of this antibiotic
しかし、この抗生物質が発明される前は
It is a drug that is commonly used by others.
他人がよく使っている薬です。
Then the main invention came from this dye
そして、主要な発明はこの染料から生まれました
Therefore, the Huanei drug found at that time was indeed
したがって、当時発見された華寧薬は確かに
inhibits the growth of bacteria
細菌の増殖を抑制します
So they started looking for it from a lot of dyes
そこで彼らはたくさんの染料の中からそれを探し始めました
Is there an active ingredient
有効成分はありますか
You all know that at that time
当時のことは皆さんもご存知でしょう
In fact, the prevention and control industry is very developed
実際、予防および制御産業は非常に発展しています。
so a lot of dye a lot of dye
とてもたくさんの染料、たくさんの染料
Then look for these drugs from the dye
次に、染料からこれらの薬物を探します
What about the first xanthamines?
最初のキサンタミンについてはどうでしょうか?
In history it is here
歴史上、それはここにあります
The entire medical surplus is called
医療余剰全体は次のように呼ばれます。
Pontosil is the drug
ポントシルは薬です
Do you know why it is called yellow amines?
なぜ黄色アミンと呼ばれるか知っていますか?
Because its English name is Sophora
英語名は Sophora なので
Because it mainly contains this xanthic acid
このキサントゲン酸が主に含まれているため
xanthates and then it adds an amine
キサンテートにアミンを加える
Drugs that are slightly not called yellow amines
イエローアミンとは少し違う薬剤
Pontosil is what we now know is a
ポントシルは現在私たちが知っているものです。
A first drug of the yellow amine class
黄色アミンクラスの最初の薬剤
to fight bacterial growth
細菌の増殖と戦うために
That in fact it is a Protide
実はプロタイドだということ
That is to say, the drug is taken into the body
つまり、薬が体内に取り込まれるということです。
Why is it called Protide?
なぜプロタイドと呼ばれるのでしょうか？
a subjunctive of the drug
薬の仮定法
That is to say, it has no function
つまり機能がない
but eat into the body
でも体に食い込む
Influenced by our body's performance metabolism
私たちの体のパフォーマンス代謝の影響を受ける
it is broken down
それは壊れています
The decomposed substances are still the ingredients of the drug.
分解された物質はまだ薬の成分です。
So it is said to be a drug lead
だから麻薬の手がかりだと言われている
Precursor Protide
前駆体プロチド
That drug is also very famous
あの薬もとても有名です
because I just said
さっき言ったから
He was before the invention of the resistance number
彼は抵抗数が発明される前にいた
He is used to fight bacterial infections
彼は細菌感染症と戦うのに慣れている
Of course he can't sterilize
もちろん消毒もできない
What about the most famous example?
最も有名な例はどうでしょうか？
is in
いる
That is to say, his example is in
つまり、彼の例は次のとおりです。
early days of war two
第二次世界大戦の初期
war two because
第二次世界大戦だから
The Second World War probably started around 1940
第二次世界大戦はおそらく 1940 年頃に始まった
in the early days because
初期の頃は
when war breaks out
戦争が勃発したとき
There will be many casualties on the field
現場では多くの死傷者が出ることになる
So if you ever watch those war movies
それで、もしあなたがそれらの戦争映画を見たことがあるなら、
like saving private lane
プライベートレーンを保存するようなもの
or some war movies
あるいは戦争映画とか
If you listen carefully to his dialogue
彼の会話を注意深く聞いてみると
you will listen carefully when that
そのときは注意深く聞いてください
When the soldiers are defeated by me, they will call conscripts, and then they will say "sweep the light file, sweep the light file or sweep the light file"
兵士たちが私に負けると徴兵を呼び、「光のファイルを掃討せよ、光のファイルを掃討せよ、あるいは光のファイルを掃討せよ」と言うだろう。
That is to say
つまり
He's hurt, hurry up and use this drug
彼は怪我をしている、急いでこの薬を使ってください
to treat his wound
彼の傷を治療するために
in the early days
初めの頃
is very important to use
使用することが非常に重要です
The other most famous is
他に最も有名なのは、
He once saved the prime minister this autumn
彼はこの秋にかつて首相を救ったことがある
s life
的生命
why
なぜ
Because I just told him that on the battlefield
戦場でそう言っただけだから
just a lot of soldiers
ただたくさんの兵士
Other guns also include autumn
他の銃にも秋が含まれます
Why? This is of course a picture of Churchill
なぜか? これはもちろんチャーチルの写真です
Everyone, if you look at the photos of historical phenomena
みなさん、歴史的現象の写真を見てみると
He already has a tall hat we're used to
彼はすでに私たちが見慣れている高い帽子をかぶっています
But Churchill
しかしチャーチル
Nathan Churchill
ネイサン・チャーチル
because at the time in the UK
なぜなら当時イギリスでは
Of course he is here
もちろん彼はここにいます
he is a brelian
彼はブレリアンです
At that time, Britain had many colonies
当時、イギリスには多くの植民地がありました
including north africa
北アフリカも含めて
Everyone knows that Germany was
当時のドイツは誰もが知っています
Except in aggression in the European battlefield
ヨーロッパの戦場での侵略を除いて
They go to fight, say, Belgium, Holland, France
彼らは戦いに行く、例えばベルギー、オランダ、フランス
Even ended up going to Russia
結局ロシアにも行ってしまった
In addition, Germany at that time
また、当時のドイツでは、
Originally based on British colonies on the other side of Africa
もともとはアフリカの反対側にあるイギリスの植民地に拠点を置いていた
At that time, Britain had a lot of colonies in North Africa
当時、イギリスは北アフリカに多くの植民地を持っていました。
Then Germany will be killed
そうすればドイツは滅びるだろう
His most famous tank army
彼の最も有名な戦車軍団
The general of the Tank Club is called Longmener
戦車クラブの将軍はロングメナーと呼ばれます
He uses the tank company
彼は戦車中隊を利用している
Use them to say Longmener
ロングメナーと言うために使用します
he is a stranger
彼は見知らぬ人です
He uses tank club tactics
彼は戦車クラブの戦術を使用します
can rarely north africa
まれに北アフリカにできる
Because the terrain in North Africa is flat
北アフリカは地形が平坦なので、
So the war is already urgent
つまり戦争はすでに切迫している
So autumn is also very tense
秋もとても緊張しますね
He went to Tunisia in North Africa to investigate
彼は調査のために北アフリカのチュニジアに行きました
Because of course if the leader goes, it can calm down the troops
もちろんリーダーが行けば軍隊を落ち着かせることができるから
When I went, I wanted to say
行ったら言いたかった
Positive economics to see if the British army can
イギリス軍ができるかどうかを確かめるポジティブ経済学
Able to face off against the German army
ドイツ軍と対決可能
I never thought that when he was in Tunicia
彼がチュニジアにいたときはそんなこと考えもしなかった
he has an infection
彼は感染症にかかっています
this infection is very serious
この感染症は非常に深刻です
So at that time, a sick notice was issued.
それでそのとき、病気の通知が出されました。
So of course he can't let Germany know
だからもちろん彼はドイツに知らせることはできない
germany they are happy to say
ドイツ 彼らは喜んでこう言います
British Prime Minister may soon be knocked out
英国首相は間もなく失脚するかもしれない
So by that time his daughter had already flown from the UK
つまり、その時までに彼の娘はすでに英国から飛行機で帰国していました
to Tunicia beside him
彼の隣にあるチュニジアへ
Because at that time Churchill was already ill.
なぜなら、その時チャーチルはすでに病気だったからです。
A sickness notice has been issued
病気届が出されました
didn't expect them
彼らは期待していなかった
That is to say, the doctor Churchill used this wind-sweeping dragon
つまり、チャーチル医師はこの風を払う竜を使ったのです。
Because at that time, Panning Xining had not yet been mass-produced.
なぜなら当時、パンニング西寧はまだ量産化されていなかったからです。
I'll talk about it later
それについては後で話します
So they are using Ponosio
彼らはPonosioを使用しています
It turned out that Churchill's life was successfully saved.
チャーチルの命は無事に救われたことが判明した。
That means he's responding to the drug, too.
つまり、彼もその薬に反応しているということだ。
It's his blood that doesn't work
機能しないのは彼の血だ
so he can come alive
そうすれば彼は生き返ることができる
then later
じゃあ後で
Because he can't announce it during the war
戦争中は発表できないから
But he followed the radio in the newspaper
しかし彼は新聞のラジオを追った
he just talked
彼はただ話したばかりです
i have a small situation in tunicia
チュニジアでちょっとした事情があるのですが
But luckily it’s because it’s Flaming
でも幸運なことに、それはFlamingだからです
Because Flaming is a British Panlin series invention
フレーミングはイギリスのパンリンシリーズの発明だから
so saved my life
それで私の命は救われました
Because he doesn't admit that Pontos has
彼はポントスが持っていることを認めていないからです
Because Pontos has this drug
ポントスにはこの薬があるから
It's the yellow and blue drug, Bayer in Germany
黄色と青の薬、ドイツのバイエルです
So in terms of this moral
したがって、この道徳の観点から言えば、
Of course because Britain was at war with Germany
もちろんイギリスはドイツと戦争中だったので
He absolutely can't say it's a drug invented by the Germans
彼はそれがドイツ人によって発明された薬であるとは絶対に言えません
he must have said
彼は言ったに違いない
i have a problem in north africa
北アフリカで問題がある
Fortunately, it was given to me by Flaming's protest department.
幸いなことに、それはフレーミングの抗議部門から私に与えられました。
saved my life
私の命を救いました
So but the fact
だから、しかし事実
Later Deng Ming actually
後の鄧明は実は
Churchill killed Huang
チャーチルは黄を殺害した
Their government affairs killed Huang
彼らの政務が黄を殺害した
In fact, it was the Germans Bayer who produced it
実際、それを製造したのはドイツのバイエル社でした
This yellow and blue drug saved Churchill's life
この黄色と青の薬はチャーチルの命を救った
It's a very famous story
とても有名な話です
then again
また
His name is Penningsillin
彼の名前はペニンシリンです
I just talked about Penning Xilin
先ほどペニン・ザイリンについて話しました
He is the first resistance aid in our human body
彼は私たち人間の体の最初の抵抗補助者です
It's a drug that can treat bacterial infections
細菌感染症を治療する薬です
can be sterilized
滅菌可能
The inventor, of course, was Alexander Freyming
発明者はもちろんアレクサンダー・フライミングです
That's Freyming
それがフレミングです
Because of his later contributions to human medicine
彼のその後の人間の医学への貢献により、
He was called SIR by the wind
彼は風によってSIRと呼ばれた
That's this penning cillin
それがこのペニング・シリンです
Our question is of course Penningsillin
私たちの質問はもちろんペニンシリンです
He is usually called Cin-E-S-U
彼は通常 Cin-E-S-U と呼ばれます
His structure is quite unique
彼の構造は非常にユニークです
That's for chemistry
それは化学用です
Because of his four-five-ring structure
四五環構造なので
is a very strange
とても奇妙です
when he invented
彼が発明したとき
no one believes in this structure
誰もこの構造を信じていない
So until 1928
それで1928年まで
Freyming discovered
フレイミング発見
found out
見つけた
Afterwards they managed to save the dormitory
その後、彼らはなんとか寮を救った
Structural identification of Nathan's chemical
ネイサンズケミカルの構造同定
I just said this about chemicals
先ほど化学物質について言いました
it is a very unstable structure
それは非常に不安定な構造です
until the 1950s
1950年代まで
There's Dorothy that
ドロシーがいるよ
good
良い
He just used x-ray to explain
彼は説明するためにX線を使っただけだ
to really decide on his structure
彼の構造を実際に決定する
But why is he called Omeshu
しかし、なぜ彼はオメシュと呼ばれるのですか？
Because Fleming knows
フレミングは知っているから
He found this plum fungus
彼はこの梅菌を見つけました
Plum fungus
梅菌
Because of Plum fungus
梅菌のせいで
The identified chemical
特定された化学物質
green plum tree
緑の梅の木
So usually you will see in literature or books
通常、文献や本で見ることができます
Some people call it Penisening
それをペニスニングと呼ぶ人もいます
Because or called green plum tree
または青梅の木と呼ばれるため
Actually he's just the same thing
実は彼も同じなんです
Then this is our Dr. Fleming
それでは、こちらが私たちのフレミング博士です
And then of course their interest in human
そしてもちろん人間への興味も
made a great contribution
多大な貢献をした
will definitely get a nobel prize
間違いなくノーベル賞を受賞するだろう
so we will see today
それでは今日見てみましょう
Getu with a lot of bell awards
ベル賞多数のゲトゥ
Because of his ELF research and development
彼のELFの研究開発のため
has a great contribution
大きな貢献をしています
of course i just mentioned
もちろん今言いました
Fleming was in 1928
フレミングは1928年に
He discovered this phenomenon
彼はこの現象を発見した
That's just that Penisening
それはまさにペニセニングです
This green plum tree itself is not very stable
この青梅の木自体はあまり安定していません
So there are actually some problems in purification
つまり、浄化には実際にはいくつかの問題があります
Later, because the people under him were
その後、彼の下の人々が
Froory and Chain
フロリーとチェーン
Rich and Froory
リッチ＆フロリー
these two people they are
この二人は彼らです
is his research
彼の研究です
Browning's research caught his attention
ブラウニングの研究が彼の注意を引いた
So they keep putting this
それで彼らはこれを置き続けます
This green plum tree, this chemical substance
この青梅、この化学物質
saved successfully
正常に保存
And try to figure out how to do production
そして生産を行う方法を考えてみてください
That's because of the contributions of the two of them
それはお二人の貢献のおかげです
That's why this green plum tree can produce in large quantities
だからこの青梅は大量に実るのです
Able to provide medical use
医療用途にも対応可能
So these three scientists in 1945
1945 年のこの 3 人の科学者は
get the nobel prize
ノーベル賞をもらう
Look at 1945
1945年を見てください
when the war was just over
戦争が終わったばかりのとき
So he got this Nobel Prize in Physiology or Medicine
それで彼はノーベル生理学・医学賞を受賞しました
Where is his contribution?
彼の貢献はどこにあるのでしょうか？
Froory Discovered Plain City
フロリーが平原都市を発見
It is because of the invention of the green plum tree
青梅の発明のせいだ
Being able to come to this for all kinds of this
あらゆる種類のこれのためにここに来ることができること
Infectious diseases have a therapeutic effect
感染症には治療効果がある
so they got the nobel prize
それで彼らはノーベル賞を受賞した
let me tell you now
今教えてください
its mechanism of action
その作用機序
Pan Lin's soul
パン・リンの魂
Just mentioned that if we're looking for a drug today
先ほども言いましたが、今日薬を探しているとしたら
What about the drug?
薬はどうですか？
because it is against bacterial infections
細菌感染症を防ぐため
It is good if it has no side effects
副作用がなければ良いのですが
it should be selective
それは選択的であるべきです
That is to say, the drug
つまりその薬は
Can't have any effect on humans
人間には何の影響も与えられない
must not be toxic to humans
人間に有毒であってはなりません
But directly
でも直接的には
And only to sterilize
そして殺菌するだけ
So we're going to find out
それで調べてみます
How is this bacterium different from a human?
この細菌は人間とどう違うのでしょうか？
that's good
それは良い
Fortunately, that is to say
幸いなことに、つまり、
What about our human cells and bacteria?
私たち人間の細胞や細菌はどうなるのでしょうか？
its difference
その違い
The biggest difference is the bacterial cell B
最大の違いは細菌細胞Bです
So the most important function of elasticity
したがって、弾性の最も重要な機能は
is deeply synthesized in bacterial cells B
細菌細胞内で深く合成される B
what about this picture
この写真はどうですか
It's actually a Staphylococcus aureus
実は黄色ブドウ球菌なんです
that you know
あなたが知っていること
Regardless of the lowly bacteria
下等な細菌ならともかく
to our higher human cells
私たちの高等な人間の細胞へ
what about all bacteria or cells
すべての細菌や細胞についてはどうでしょうか
it will have this cell membrane
この細胞膜があるでしょう
Membrane to put the internal environment of this creature
この生物の内部環境を整える膜
Isolate from the outside world
外界から隔離する
We say it's a cell membrane
それは細胞膜だと言います
For bacteria
細菌にとっては
What about Staphylococcus aureus?
黄色ブドウ球菌についてはどうですか？
he is a bacterium
彼は細菌です
Then he has a thick layer of cell arms on the outside
そして外側には細胞腕の厚い層がある
What is the energy of this cell arm?
この細胞腕のエネルギーは何ですか?
It is a function of structural support
それは構造的サポートの機能です
Why
なぜ
Because the bacteria itself has to face the inside and outside of the cell
細菌自体が細胞の内側と外側に向き合わなければならないため
because he maintains a
なぜなら彼は
a physiological
一個生理
That is to say, one of his various substances
つまり、彼のさまざまな物質のうちの 1 つ
He has to maintain a certain concentration
彼は一定の集中力を維持しなければならない
So he has some osmotic pressure
つまり彼には浸透圧があるのです
That is to say, the inside and outside of the cell
つまり、細胞の内側と外側
his
他的
his concentration is different
彼の集中力は違う
So he has a pressure that penetrates him
だから彼には浸透するプレッシャーがある
So if you don't have a strong
だから、強い力を持っていないなら、
supported by a cell arm
セルアームで支えられている
He can't help that bacteria
彼はその細菌を助けることができない
catch directly
直接捕まえる
left thick
剩厚厚
so he bursts again
それで彼はまた爆発した
Moisture keeps coming in and it will burst
湿気が入り続けて破裂してしまう
so what
だから何
Rehearsing the mind today is actually mainly in
今日の心のリハーサルは、実は主に
A synthesis of the cell arm of the main segment
メインセグメントの細胞アームの合成
prevent him from building him well
だから彼は彼をうまく組み立てることができない
What kind of structure is the cell arm of bacteria?
細菌の細胞腕はどのような構造になっているのでしょうか？
it's hard for you to say
あなたが言うのは難しいです
Today he is a 3D
今日の彼は3Dです
A network structure in a three-dimensional space
3次元空間のネットワーク構造
that he is a
彼は
quite complex aggregate molecule
非常に複雑な凝集分子
That is you can say it as saying
つまり、こう言うことができます
If this is a two-figure
これが2桁なら
If this is a sugar body
これが糖体なら
a polysaccharide
多糖類
a chain of sugar
砂糖の鎖
each one is a
それぞれが
a polymer of sugar
砂糖のポリマー
What about between each chain?
各チェーン間はどうなるのでしょうか？
must be concatenated
連結する必要があります
then it will have
そうすればそれはあるでしょう
Its structure has its strength
その構造には強度があります
that sugar body
その砂糖の体
What about the sugar molecules?
糖分子はどうなるのでしょうか？
It must use the ecological key to make a series connection
直列接続するにはエコキーを使用する必要があります
that is, as if you were
つまり、あたかもあなたがそうであるかのように
Do this like a past event
過去のイベントのようにこれを実行します
your
あなたの
Both vertical and horizontal must be wired
垂直方向と水平方向の両方に配線する必要があります
then contact each other
それからお互いに連絡して
that this
これは
The sugar molecules in the vertical direction have to be connected in series with each other
縦方向の糖分子は互いに直列に接続されている必要があります
Need to use ecology
エコロジーを利用する必要がある
Then this series of steps
では、この一連の手順を
In fact, in the whole deep synthesis
実際、深層合成全体において、
last step
最後のステップ
Well, it just so happens that the Chinese New Year is at the last step.
さて、たまたま旧正月も最後の段階にあります。
make it impossible to connect
接続できなくする
So even though it frames this
したがって、これをフレーム化したとしても、
What about sugar polymers?
糖ポリマーについてはどうですか？
But it can't connect well
でもうまく接続できない
so
それで
If you use this barbarian today for New Year's
今日の新年にこのバーバリアンを使用する場合
When rehearsing sex, his cell arms are not well connected with each other
セックスのリハーサル中、彼の独房の腕は互いにうまく接続されていません
Bacteria with such a soft structure can easily swell and die
このような柔らかい構造を持つ細菌は、容易に膨張して死滅する可能性があります。
So this is the main mechanism of rehearsal sex
これがリハーサルセックスの主なメカニズムです
How did he discover such a phenomenon
彼はどのようにしてそのような現象を発見したのか
It was actually an unexpected discovery that we ended up coming back
結局戻ってきたのは、実は予期せぬ発見だった
But the most important thing is that Dr. Flaming carefully noticed such a problem
しかし、最も重要なことは、フレーミング博士がそのような問題に注意深く気づいたことです
Then add the weather is also a factor
次に、天候も要素として追加します
why?
なぜ？
My work is back to September 1928
私の仕事は1928年9月に遡ります。
At that time, Fleming went on vacation in August
その時、フレミングは8月に休暇を取りました
If you all know Fleming himself, although he was already famous at that time
フレミング自身をご存知の方はご存知でしょうが、彼は当時すでに有名でした。
But is he doing the experiment clean?
しかし、彼は実験をクリーンに行っているでしょうか?
Why do you guys take a look
なんで君たち見てみるの？
you will see this photo this is not a fake photo
この写真が表示されますが、これは偽物の写真ではありません
You can see that the rows at the back are all the culture names of his bacteria.
後ろの行はすべて彼の細菌の文化名であることがわかります。
So after he finished the experiment, he is usually what we say is very annoying to him.
そのため、彼が実験を終えた後、彼は通常、私たちが彼にとって非常に迷惑だと言うものです。
A researcher just piled it on
研究者がそれを積み上げただけ
so what
だから何
before he let go
彼が手放す前に
he finished the experiment
彼は実験を終えた
he has painted some on it
彼はそれに絵を描いた
some golden yellow grapes
いくつかの黄金色のブドウ
Just took some experiments on bacterial culture
細菌培養の実験を行ったところです
finished
終了した
He just put it on the lab table and walked away
彼はそれを実験台の上に置いて立ち去った
then come back after a while
それからしばらくして戻ってくる
so he went out to play in august
それで彼は8月に遊びに行きました
then come back in september
それから9月にまた来てください
that's just right
それはちょうどいいです
his bacterial culture
彼の細菌培養
Because we usually do bacterial cultures
普段細菌培養を行っているため
To avoid the interference of other bacteria
他の菌の干渉を避けるため
so usually have a cover
なので通常はカバーがあります
I didn't expect him to leave before
以前は彼が去るとは予想していませんでした
He did not throw away the experiment
彼は実験を捨てなかった
Even the lid is open for some
蓋が開いている人もいる
came back to find out that
それを知るために戻ってきた
what happened
どうしたの
opened the lid inside
中の蓋を開けた
Invasion of other species
他種の侵入
he noticed
彼は気が付いた
if everyone can't see
みんなが見えなかったら
If students like mine see this situation
もし私のような学生がこの状況を見たら
or me
それともわたし
just to see other pollution
他の汚染を見るためだけに
he has dropped it
彼はそれを落とした
But he feels very different
しかし、彼はまったく違うと感じています
because strange
奇妙だから
He's got a bunch of bacteria all over it.
全身にバクテリアがいっぱい付いているんです。
But once this strain is added
しかし、このひずみが追加されると、
Strange that it seems next to
隣に見えるのが不思議だ
No bacteria can survive here
ここでは細菌は生き残ることができません
So he is tantamount to noticing that
だから彼はそれに気づいているのと同じだ
he must be a microbe
彼は微生物に違いない
Then this microbe will produce a substance
そして、この微生物は物質を生産します
Can have a bactericidal effect
殺菌効果が期待できる
So it's like being here
だからここにいるようなもの
These are full of bacteria
これらは細菌でいっぱいです
bacteria taking place
細菌が発生している
He then backed off
それから彼は後退した
Because of the existence of this species back off
この種の存在のおかげで
So he noticed this phenomenon
それで彼はこの現象に気づきました
so he thinks
それで彼は考えます
He later identified that it was a plum fungus
その後、それが梅菌であることが判明した
Nomeella because it competes with bacteria
ノミーラは細菌と競合するため
Because it is covered with soil and has nutrients
土に覆われていて栄養分があるので
We say this cultivator
この修煉者を私たちは修煉者と言います
Then they have to compete for the training machine
その後、トレーニングマシンを争わなければなりません
So Mei bacteria distinguish some substances
つまり、メイ細菌はいくつかの物質を区別します
It's like saying this is my domain
これは私のドメインだと言っているようなものです
you can't come
あなたは来られません
So the bacteria are all dead.
したがって、細菌はすべて死滅します。
So there must be a chemical substance
だから化学物質が存在するはずだ
Chemicals have a bactericidal effect
化学薬品には殺菌効果がある
That, of course, later led to his discovery.
もちろん、それが後の彼の発見につながりました。
the Panicia
パニシア
that's what i just said
それが私が今言ったことです
why climate is a major factor
なぜ気候が主要な要因なのか
Because of the growth of bacteria he needs
彼が必要とする細菌の増殖のため
I also know that it needs to be in a high heat environment
高温環境に置く必要があることもわかっています
So it happens to be the rotating weather in August
つまり、8月は天気が変わりやすいのです
Bacteria in this summer environment
この夏の環境の細菌
bacteria grow happily
細菌が楽しく増殖する
But it just happened to take turns
でもそれはたまたま順番が変わっただけだ
It was a cold day for a while
久しぶりに寒い日が続きましたね
that cold weather
あの寒い天気
especially cold weather
特に寒い季節
Because the humidity over there is quite high.
あそこは湿度がかなり高いから。
Therefore, it is very conducive to the growth of Mei fungus
したがって、メイ菌の増殖に非常に適しています。
So there was a summer weather
それで夏の天気になりました
make this bacteria grow really well
このバクテリアをよく増殖させます
Just after that there was an invasion of plum fungus
その直後に梅菌の侵入があった
Then there's another cold air
その後、また冷たい空気が入ってきました
Bacterial growth is inhibited
細菌の増殖が抑制される
Then the fungus starts to grow
すると菌が増殖し始める
So there is such an obvious contrast
こんなに明らかなコントラストがあるのですね
The result of such an obvious contrast
このような明らかなコントラストの結果
Let Fu Nanmin know
フー・ナンミンに知らせてください
And he said carefully
そして彼は慎重に言った
this is not rubbish
これはゴミではありません
It's not trash, it's not meant to be thrown away right away
ゴミではありません、すぐに捨てられるものではありません
Rather, it is an interesting phenomenon
むしろ面白い現象です
He himself said that instead of thinking about finding out
彼自身も、調べようと考えるのではなく、
What kind of a dimensional creature is this?
これは一体何の次元生物なのでしょうか？
It turned out to be a plum fungus
梅菌だったことが判明
So we can say that he is a very unexpected
したがって、彼は非常に予想外の人物であると言えます
an event
イベント
and very lucky
そしてとても幸運です
And he is the most important thing to observe carefully
そして彼は注意深く観察することが最も重要です
get such a discovery
そんな発見を得る
Of course Pan Senji
もちろんパン・センジ
we just talked
私たちはちょうど話したばかりです
There will be a Jibang in the back
後ろにはジバンがいるよ
It is Foreign and Chains
外国人とチェーン店です
These two he began to explain
この二つについて彼は説明し始めた
Oh, found this phenomenon
ああ、こんな現象発見
He removed the bill of materials
彼は部品表を削除した
Then prove that this is green plum tree
じゃあこれが青梅だということを証明してください
what about the problem
問題はどうですか
What if he can sterilize
消毒できたらどうなるか
He can certainly deal with bacterial infections
彼は確かに細菌感染症に対処できる
The question is how to apply it to people
問題はそれを人にどう応用するかだ
Because by then
なぜならそれまでに
Bacterial infection is a
細菌感染症というのは、
basically a testimonial
基本的には証言
It's kind of like we got HIV now
今ではHIVに感染しているようなものです
AIDS is the same as encountering this Cancer
エイズはこのガンに遭遇するのと同じです
basically unknown evidence
基本的に不明な証拠
So at that time there was a big
それで、その時、大きな出来事がありました
an effort is to say how
努力とはどうやって言うかということです
to mass produce it
それを量産するために
Then let me tell you that the data is
それから、データは次のとおりであることを教えてください。
He discovered in 1928
彼は 1928 年に発見しました
But by 1942
しかし1942年までに
All over the United States and the entire Pensenkey's
アメリカ全土とペンセンキー全体
The total output can only be one dead patient
合計出力は死亡患者 1 名のみです
Because it cannot be mass-produced
大量生産できないので
because i just said
私が今言ったばかりだから
Panlin Xinyu itself has many problems.
Panlin Xinyu自体には多くの問題があります。
The first one is unstable, how do you produce it
最初のものは不安定ですが、どうやって作成しますか
the second is
2番目は
And another question is that
そしてもう一つの疑問は、
What about its absorption in the body?
体内での吸収はどうなのでしょうか？
The most original version of Panlin Xinyu is
Panlin Xinyu の最もオリジナルなバージョンは次のとおりです。
Not easily absorbed in the body
体内に吸収されにくい
Probably only two to three two percent can be absorbed
おそらく 2 ～ 3 2% しか吸収されないでしょう
So most of it is drained
なのでほとんどが排水されてしまいます
equal to if you give it
与えれば等しい
For example, eating a ground
たとえば、地面を食べると、
A word of Pan Lin's heart
パン・リンの心の言葉
About two or three hundred milligrams will go away
約200～300ミリグラムが消えます
So, when it was time to do Pan Lin Xin Yu
それで、Pan Lin Xin Yuをやるときは
Patient's urine shadow it goes to recycling
患者の尿影はリサイクルされる
because it passes into the urine
尿の中にも出てくるので
Look at Taiwan's storage and recycling
台湾の保管とリサイクルを見てみましょう
If not, the whole
そうでない場合は、全体
Because you have 70% to 80% of Pan Lin Xinyu wasted
Pan Lin Xinyu の 70% ～ 80% が無駄になっているため、
this is a serious problem
これは深刻な問題です
So at that time
だからその時は
And it stays in the body for a short time
そして体内に短期間留まる
So it's all downsides of the drug
つまり、それはすべてこの薬のマイナス面です
So fortunately Pan Lin Xinyu discovered it by accident
幸いなことに、Pan Lin Xinyu はそれを偶然発見しました。
From a modern perspective
現代の視点から見ると
This Pan Lin Xinyu must be abandoned
この潘林新宇は捨てるべきだ
because it doesn't meet our requirements
それは私たちの要件を満たしていないため
it has a low absorption rate
吸収率が低いです
Then and easily in the body
そして簡単に体内に
only three or four hours but not good
たった3、4時間だけど良くない
Then you need to pay attention
それから注意が必要です
This Fulhamming he is in England
このフルハミング、彼はイギリスにいます
so that england is at war
だからイギリスは戦争中だ
And the UK especially rounds every day
そして英国は特に毎日ラウンドします
to the German bombing
ドイツ軍の爆撃に
Basically, the country will send people
基本的には国が人を送り込む
So they went to talk to the British government
そこで彼らは英国政府と話し合いに行きました
Can you come to produce panxing
パンシンをプロデュースしに来てくれませんか
Because we don't have the strength
私たちには力がないから
And at that time there was still a doubt that
そして当時はまだ疑問がありました
At that time, the three recommended
その時に3人が勧めたのが、
That seems to be Frolly he claims
それはフロリーのようだ、と彼は主張する
We're going to take this pattern
このパターンでいきます
Because this will definitely sell well in the future
これは将来必ず売れるから
Fortunately, Fulhamming and Chain objected
幸いなことに、フルハミングとチェインは反対した
Said this is if it can be used like this
こんな風に使えたらこれだよって言ってた
make a significant contribution to human well-being
人間の幸福に大きく貢献する
So they refuse to pattern
だから彼らはパターン化することを拒否する
so what
だから何
Fulhamming he is generous
フルハミング氏は寛大だ
He sent the county chief to people everywhere.
彼は郡長を各地の人々に派遣した。
See if it can be applied
適用できるかどうかを確認する
So they just have to go to America to find
だから彼らはアメリカに行って見つければいいだけだ
so America
だからアメリカ
They came across this like a gift from the sky
彼らは空からの贈り物のようにこれに出会った
they are happy
彼らは満足している
So the various plans in it
それで、その中のさまざまな計画
to find a good county chief
良い郡長を見つけるために
So they later in E-NOR
それで彼らは後にE-NORを始めました
likely that
おそらくそれ
Wang Furen at the market in Enoi
エノイの市場にいる王福仁氏
find a rotten cantaloupe
腐ったマスクメロンを見つける
The green plum mushrooms on the rotten cantaloupe
腐ったマスクメロンの上にある青梅キノコ
Proven to be one of the best strains
最高の株の1つであることが証明されています
Because the output is very high
出力が非常に高いので、
and
と
Back then Midwest farming was fresh
当時中西部の農業は新鮮だった
so they later found out
それで彼らは後で知りました
because a lot of corn is grown in the Midwest
中西部ではトウモロコシがたくさん栽培されているため、
It turns out they found that the corn
彼らはトウモロコシを発見したことが判明しました
There will be a lot of emissions in the province of turning into cornmeal
コーンミールに変わる地域では大量の排出物が発生するだろう
this boiling water
この沸騰したお湯
This boiling water is used
この沸騰したお湯が使われます
Do this Plum Fermentation
梅発酵をしてみよう
its yield is very very good
収量は非常に良いです
so
それで
one like this
このようなもの
As a result of optimization, its yield is the original
最適化の結果、収量は元の値になります
Disk Venus found more than 100,000 times
Disk Venus は 100,000 回以上発見されました
So by 1942, the entire U.S. production could only be used by 10 patients
そのため、1942 年までに米国の全生産量は 10 人の患者にしか使用できなくなりました。
By 1943
1943年までに
that time
その時
they can be mass produced
それらは大量生産することができます
so until
だからそれまで
I'll talk about the next one first
まずは次回の話をします
So until 1944
つまり1944年まで
what about them at that time
そのとき彼らはどうだったのか
can already know
すでに知ることができます
2.3 million doses of this
これを230万回分
this dose
この用量
So there's enough for over 2 million doses
つまり200万回以上の投与量に十分な量がある
You can live until 1942 with only 10 patients available
10人の患者がいれば1942年まで生きられる
So it is now possible to produce doses up to 230
したがって、最大 230 回の線量を生成することが可能になりました。
So everyone came to the United States
それでみんなアメリカに来たんだ
When the whole Confederates landed from France
南軍全員がフランスから上陸したとき
heavy casualties
多大な死傷者
So they can heal the casualty with resistance
彼らは抵抗力を持って負傷者を治癒できるようにする
Well, this is already known to everyone
まあ、これはもう皆さんご存知のことですが、
They have estimated that there is Pandey's influence
彼らはパンディの影響があると推定している
So what about Confederate soldiers?
それでは南軍兵士はどうなるのでしょうか？
His casualty rate has been reduced by 12 to 15 percent
彼の死傷率は 12 ～ 15 パーセント減少しました
then you'll see this is changing the history of war
そうすれば、これが戦争の歴史を変えていることがわかるだろう
Because at this time in Germany they only used Huang Ah Nei's medicine Pontosio
なぜなら、当時ドイツでは黄阿寧の薬であるポントシオしか使用されていなかったからです。
That's the Confederates already have Pandy Sydney.
つまり南軍にはすでにパンディ・シドニーがいるということだ。
And there are millions of doses
そして何百万もの投与量があります
So the difference between the two sides is
したがって、両者の違いは次のとおりです
The soldiers of the German side were injured
ドイツ側の兵士が負傷した
Probably depends on how good his immune system is.
おそらく彼の免疫システムがどれだけ優れているかに依存します。
But here you have antibiotics to treat
でもここには治療のための抗生物質がある
So at that time there was a poster
そのときポスターがありました
You see three genera pandy sydney
3属のパンディ・シドニーが見えます
thought there was come home
家に帰ってきたと思った
because he was hurt
彼は怪我をしたから
But because of proper handling, he will still return to the plane.
しかし、適切に対処したため、彼はまだ飛行機に戻ります。
The other one is a very famous experiment in 193
もう一つは193年の非常に有名な実験です。
Then everyone see this is a little girl
それからみんな見て、これは小さな女の子だよ
You see she was healed in the end
彼女は最終的には癒されたのがわかります
it's a normal little girl
それは普通の小さな女の子です
But at the beginning, there was a serious sense of narrative
しかし、最初は深刻な物語の感覚がありました
Look at him, this, this, this eye clip is next to his eye
彼を見てください、これ、これ、このアイクリップと彼の目の横
This wound is almost festering badly.
この傷はひどく化膿しそうになっている。
You see, this is after adding Penning psychology
ほら、これはペニング心理学を追加した後です
his medical effects
彼の医療効果
You will see the wound gradually shrink
傷が徐々に縮んでいくのがわかります
Then this side has already started to the whole domain now
すると、こちら側はすでにドメイン全体に向けて動き始めています
Then there is still some swelling here basically.
それから、基本的にここにはまだいくらかの腫れがあります。
But basically the wound has gradually disappeared.
でも基本的に傷は徐々に消えてきました。
So you basically end up late
だから基本的に遅刻してしまうんです
you can barely see the wound
傷はほとんど見えません
So this is a very famous experiment
これは非常に有名な実験です
It's like adding Pan Ning's psychology to the body
潘寧の心理学を体に加えたようなものです
He was indeed able to deal with this delicate infection
彼は確かにこのデリケートな感染症に対処することができた
that is very famous
それはとても有名です
Then let's see the picture just above
それでは、すぐ上の写真を見てみましょう
This is just at that time one by one
これは一つずつでした
You see, everyone knows that this is Xiao Wangsun?
ほら、これがシャオ・ワンスンであることは誰もが知っていますか？
It's an ad from 1944
1944年の広告です
you look like one by one
あなたは一人一人のように見えます
Just do it on this oil drum
このオイルバレルでやるだけです
look
見て
Pandin Faith Cure Gonorrhea This is a disease
パンディン・フェイス 淋病を治す これは病気です
you see in 4 hours
4時間以内にわかります
So you see this number is very similar to now
この数字は現在と非常に似ていることがわかります
This drug can release a certain disease within 4 hours
この薬は4時間以内に特定の病気を治すことができます
然後 see your doctor today
今日医者に診てもらってください
so you see this time
それで今回はわかりますか
Because it used to be like this, of course it is a sexual disease
昔はこうだったので当然性病です
I thought it was terminal illness
末期の病気かと思った
You see pandin believe in invention he will tell you
パンディンは彼があなたに教えてくれる発明を信じているのがわかります
4 hours to complete the doctor
診察完了まで4時間
So get a doctor today
だから今日医者に診てもらってください
this is his ad
これは彼の広告です
Well, I just mentioned that on case 24
そうですね、先ほどケース 24 で言及しました。
especially at some point
特にある時点で
He has been able to produce like this because of Panding belief
彼がこのような作品を生み出すことができるのは、パンディングの信念があるからです
And then and can be millions of doses
そして、何百万回もの投与になる可能性があります
So the successful application in this battlefield
したがって、この戦場でのアプリケーションの成功は
and save many lives
そして多くの命を救います
And at the same time, he also drove the pharmaceutical industry in the United States
同時に、彼は米国の製薬産業を牽引しました。
because at the beginning it was before 24 cases
最初は24件前だったから
actually like merc
実際メルクみたい
he said it was that
彼はそれはそうだと言った
Originally, the company was actually a small company.
もともとこの会社は実は小さな会社でした。
But because at this time the United States they
しかし、現時点では米国が彼らを
Put a lot of manpower and material resources on the arms industry
兵器産業に多くの人的資源と物的資源を投入する
Because these guns, bullets, planes, and ships are all used in war
なぜなら、これらの銃、弾丸、飛行機、船はすべて戦争で使用されるからです。
because they are in the pharmaceutical industry
彼らは製薬業界にいるので
Because it takes a lot of rehearsal hearts to save military casualties
軍人の死傷者を救うには多くのリハーサルハートが必要だから
So at this time after the war they talked about
それで、戦後のこの時期に彼らは話し合った
Hey, rehearsing the mind has such a drill
ねえ、心のリハーサルにはこんなドリルがあるんだ
yes we can learn from success stories
はい、成功事例から学ぶことができます
Let's go find other medicines
他の薬を探しに行きましょう
It also has antiseptic properties
防腐作用もあります
So in our 50s, 60s, really into the 70s
つまり、50代、60代、そして70年代に至るまで
In the past twenty or thirty years
ここ20年か30年の間に
They searched for all kinds of bacteria from all over the world
彼らは世界中からあらゆる種類の細菌を探しました
including bacteria,
細菌も含めて、
Because this, for example, bacteria and bacteria are living with each other
これは、例えば細菌と細菌が共生しているからです。
That is to say, the fire is in the same environment
つまり、火は同じ環境にあります
They will naturally overcome each other
彼らは自然にお互いを克服するでしょう
then we saw
それから私たちは見ました
Why can the United States bacteria
なぜ米国では細菌が感染するのか
It is the same reason why this beautiful bacteria can be sterilized
この美しい細菌が殺菌できるのも同じ理由です
they survive
彼らは生き残る
They'll have this chemical power for each other
彼らはお互いにこの化学的な力を持っています
so what
だから何
this is only
これだけです
Just to tell you a few examples
いくつか例をお話ししますと、
For example, the Panlin Xinlin we saw just now
たとえば、先ほど見たパンリン・シンリン
it is a four five membered ring
それは四五員環です
Then this tetrahexacyclic ring is called cephalosporin
この四六環はセファロスポリンと呼ばれます
Its mechanism of action is basically the same as that of Panlin Xinlin
作用機序は基本的にパンリン・シンリンと同じです。
But let me tell you that Panlin Xinlin has many, many problems.
しかし、パンリン・シンリンには非常に多くの問題があることをお伝えしておきます。
Let's say it's one person dealing with Gram-positive bacteria
グラム陽性菌を扱う一人の人だとしましょう
That Pan Lin Xin Lin it has some instability issues
Pan Lin Xin Lin にはいくつかの不安定性の問題があります
Then this avatar
じゃあこのアバターは
Cebas Corin
セバス・コリン
this kind of hair
この種の髪
It's actually what we call the Wise Bed
それは実際にはワイズベッドと呼ばれるものです
So if you say you have a cold today
それで、今日は風邪だと言うと、
or some infection
または何らかの感染症
The doctor had an upper respiratory infection
医師は上気道感染症を患っていた
Doctors usually give you a standard prescription
医師は通常、標準的な処方箋を出します。
Cebaloxin
セバロキシン
this class of drugs
このクラスの薬
That other class
他のクラスは
For example, just said
たとえば、今言ったように、
This is Panlin Xinlin drugs
これは盤林新林薬です
but we'll talk later
でも後で話しましょう
It has the problem of bacteria itself and some resistance
細菌自体の問題とある程度の耐性があります
So it targets the drug resistance problem
つまり、薬剤耐性の問題をターゲットにしているのです
Lin Xinlin
リン・シンリン
do some chemical modification on it
それに化学修飾を加えます
So this is Panlin Xinlin, which mainly targets drug resistance.
これが、主に薬剤耐性をターゲットとする Panlin Xinlin です。
and these other drugs
そしてこれらの他の薬
For example like
たとえば次のように
carouselomine just mentioned
先ほど述べたカルーセロミン
Just started
剛開始
Didn't I have a prescription room at first?
最初から調剤室はなかったのですか？
The doctor has prescribed this carouselomine
医師はこのカルーセロミンを処方しました
In addition there is this
この他にもこんなのがあります
tetracycline
テトラサイクリン
are some commonly used
いくつかは一般的に使用されています
like in eye ointment
目の軟膏のように
Tetracyclines are often present
テトラサイクリン系薬剤が多く存在する
These are after the war
これらは戦後のものです
constant search
一定の検索
Different strains from around the world
世界中からのさまざまな菌株
came to find this compound
この化合物を見つけに来ました
ok we are done now
はい、もう終わりです
after antibiotics
抗生物質の後
we now run into this
私たちは今これに遭遇します
Problems we are currently experiencing
私たちが現在経験している問題
Because
なぜなら
Although I just said
今言ったばかりなのに
after the second year
2年目以降
twenty or thirty years
二十年か三十年
Although our scientists found
私たちの科学者は発見しましたが、
There are dozens of different antibiotics
抗生物質は何十種類もある
that looks like
それは次のようです
This war seems to be human
この戦争は人間らしい
the upper hand
上の手
Absolutely not
絶対違う
we only want certain drugs
私たちは特定の薬だけを望んでいます
if it falls
落ちたら
bacteria will die
細菌は死ぬでしょう
Not really
あまり
because I just told you
さっき言ったから
Currently encountering problem B
現在問題 B が発生しています
The problem is even bigger in this case
この場合、問題はさらに大きくなります
bacteria
細菌
we'll find some superbugs
スーパーバグをいくつか見つけます
This bacterium will kill all current resistant cases
この細菌は現在の耐性菌をすべて殺すでしょう
will produce resistance
抵抗を生むだろう
In fact, this problem existed very early
実際、この問題は非常に早くから存在していました
That is, when rehearsing for a psychologist to use
つまり、心理学者が使用するためにリハーサルをするとき
There is a problem of drug resistance when used in humans
人間に使用する場合は薬剤耐性の問題がある
Just because there are new drug molecules being invented all the time
新しい薬の分子が常に発明されているという理由だけで
So this question is ignored
したがってこの質問は無視されます
words here
ここの言葉
What strategies do bacteria have?
細菌はどのような戦略を持っているのでしょうか？
Will there be such a good antimicrobial strategy?
これほど優れた抗菌戦略は存在するのでしょうか?
Basically my side is just talking about two or three different ways
基本的に私の側は2つまたは3つの異なる方法について話しているだけです
That is to say, the bacteria have a way
つまり、細菌には方法があるのです
is that it uses a Lactamase
それはラクタマーゼを使用しているということです
That is to say, it is a decomposing enzyme
つまり分解酵素です
Which means you use rehearsal psychomedicine
つまり、リハーサル精神医学を使用しているということです
It can use it to produce a special enzyme
それを使用して特別な酵素を生成することができます
Can break down your drug molecules
薬物分子を分解できる
So it even if the drug molecule
したがって、たとえ薬物分子であっても
can go inside its bacteria to sterilize
細菌の中に入って殺菌することができる
but it can tear you apart
でもそれはあなたを引き裂く可能性があります
make you useless
あなたを役立たずにする
another one he can
もう一つ彼はできる
He doesn't need to disassemble
彼は分解する必要がない
He just takes your drug molecule
彼はあなたの薬物分子を摂取するだけです
just make it a decoration
ただの飾りにしてください
Originally this molecule of yours
もともとあなたのこの分子は
so that he can continue
彼が続けられるように
a molecule at a certain position
特定の位置にある分子
because it doesn't work anymore
もう機能しないから
he can also bacteria
彼はバクテリアもできる
He produces something like a helping
彼は助けのようなものを生み出します
bring your stuff in
荷物を持ち込んでください
just hit it outside
外で叩くだけ
Hit it outside as soon as you come in
入ったらすぐに外で叩く
so your meds never work
だからあなたの薬は決して効かない
into the bacteria
細菌の中へ
so he has all sorts of different strategies
だから彼はあらゆる種類の異なる戦略を持っています
molecules to fight our drugs
私たちの薬物と戦うための分子
What kind of strategy is there?
どのような戦略があるのでしょうか？
That is to say, bacteria basically
つまり、細菌は基本的に
It has many disadvantages than us
私たちより不利な点がたくさんあります
has many advantages
多くの利点があります
why
なぜ
From birth until our twenties
生まれてから20代まで
We often get married and have children
私たちはよく結婚して子供を産みます
The bacteria I just talked about
先ほど話した細菌
he grows very fast
彼はとても早く成長します
In twenty minutes he is a generation
20分で彼は一世代になる
start splitting
分割を開始する
that and he a lot
それと彼はたくさん
Usually like when you get a bacterial infection
通常は細菌感染症にかかったときと同じです
Your body has a population of millions of bacteria
あなたの体には何百万もの細菌が存在します
and he's easy
そして彼は簡単です
So he has mutations of all kinds
つまり彼はあらゆる種類の突然変異を持っている
aftermath
余波
sure as long as
確かにそうである限り
Let's say you have millions of different mutants
何百万もの異なるミュータントがいるとします。
As long as one can resist antibiotics
抗生物質に耐えられる限り
he survived
彼は生き残った
Let me give you a practical statistical example
実際の統計的な例を示しましょう
come talk to you
話しに来てください
This is revealed from a book
これはある本から明らかになった
that is to say today
つまり今日は
A patient enters for whatever reason
何らかの理由で患者が入ってくる
he went into the hospital
彼は病院へ行きました
what about this time
今回はどうですか
We have a few dorms here
ここにはいくつかの寮があります
Let me give you a little explanation
少し説明させてください
If it is a MS here
MSならここ
He said that for this Message in Sensitive
彼はこのメッセージについてセンシティブでこう言いました
That means he's a drug for you
つまり、彼はあなたにとって麻薬だということです
can be sensitive
敏感になる可能性がある
It means that the medicine you are taking is effective
服用している薬が効いているということです
What if R
Rだったらどうなるか
It is Message in Resistant
耐性のあるメッセージです
That is, he is a drug-resistant strain
つまり、彼は薬剤耐性株です
That means after entering the hospital
つまり入院してから
at this time
現時点では
This your length is 164 square
これはあなたの長さは164平方です
about a million bacteria
約100万個の細菌
Of course you, you, after you add the medicine
もちろんあなた、あなた、薬を加えた後
like this C8 week tone
このC8週のトーンのように
This is one of the cephalospoins we just talked about
これは先ほど話したセファロスポインの 1 つです
After adding an anti-trace element
微量元素添加後
you fight bacterial infections
あなたは細菌感染症と闘います
On the second day, most normal people and 90% of patients
2日目には、ほとんどの正常な人と90％の患者が
After two days of anti-trace treatment, you should be able to go home
2 日間の抗痕跡治療後、帰宅できるはずです
But if this patient
しかし、もしこの患者さんが
he has other problems
彼には他にも問題がある
Or he's not fully healed
それともまだ完全に治っていないのか
he has to be taken inside the hospital
彼は病院に運ばれなければならない
So at this time they also went to study
それでこの時、彼らも勉強に行きました
The bacteria in this patient are starting to change.
この患者の細菌は変化し始めています。
why? just started you are
なぜ? 始めたばかりです
Sensitive to this drug
この薬に対して過敏症
can be cured
治すことができます
At the beginning, if you are drug-resistant, MRSA
まず、薬剤耐性がある場合は、MRSA
if resistant
耐性がある場合
The doctor said it's okay if it's resistant
医師は耐性があるなら大丈夫だと言いました
I use other drugs
他の薬を使っている
Several different drugs may be added
いくつかの異なる薬剤が追加される場合があります
After adding it to a week later
追加してから1週間後
If you can heal and go home, you'll be fine.
治って帰れるなら大丈夫ですよ。
If the body is still very bad
まだ体の調子が悪い場合
At this time you will see all the strains
この時点で、すべての株が表示されます
Originally, only a small number of bacterial strains here were resistant to antibiotics.
もともと、ここでは少数の細菌株のみが抗生物質に耐性がありました。
Here are all the strains are so-called MR
ここにある株はすべていわゆるMRです
Staphylococcus aureus
黄色ブドウ球菌
And the trees that spawned were originally from 1,000,000
そして、生まれた木はもともと1,000,000本からのものでした
Now change to 1000
ここで 1000 に変更します
like trees come back again
木々が再び戻ってくるように
At this time, if you are not yet valid
現時点ではまだ有効でない場合は、
Even if you still have to lie in the hospital
たとえまだ病院で横たわっていなければならないとしても
this time you will use this
今回はこれを使います
venomoxin we passed
ヴェノモキシンを渡しました
Basically the last line of defense
基本的には最終防衛線
Then if it works at this time, it works
じゃあ、現時点でうまくいったら、うまくいきます
if not valid
有効でない場合
You have to stay in the patient for 20 days
20日間入院しなければならない
you at this time the drug
あなたはこの時点では麻薬です
Basically this bacteria is a superbug
基本的にこの細菌はスーパーバグです
so of course we
だからもちろん私たちも
I don't think there will be any problems here
ここで問題はないと思います
that is to say
つまり
why some people end up
なぜ一部の人は終わってしまうのか
because some of the people he was very sick
人々の中には彼が非常に病気になっていた人もいたので、
or he's clearly vulnerable
あるいは彼は明らかに脆弱だ
chemotherapy patients
化学療法患者
or very elderly patients
または非常に高齢の患者
This one of his is clearly already fragile
彼のこれは明らかにすでに壊れやすいです
So if you stay in the hospital for a long time at this time
ですから、現時点で長期入院する場合には、
Because the hospital you have been giving drugs
病院が薬を出し続けるから
Those antioxidants are constantly mutated
これらの抗酸化物質は常に変異しています
have that
それを持っています
Opportunity to choose
選択の機会
so what
だから何
Finally, if you have been lying on the ice sheet,
最後に、もしあなたが氷床の上に横たわっていたら、
finally maybe basically
最後可能基本上
All antibiotics are ineffective
すべての抗生物質は無効です
this is a very dire situation
これは非常に悲惨な状況です
the other one
別のもの
when I introduce you
あなたを紹介するとき
This is also a statistical figure
これも統計上の数字です
we can talk about this
これについて話せます
anticorrosion
防食
Continuing the fight against this infection
この感染症との戦いは続く
do not stop
不中止
why
なぜ
Because when we usually take antibiotics
なぜなら、私たちが通常抗生物質を服用するとき、
Usually we are very suspicious
通常、私たちは非常に疑い深いです
For example, today we
たとえば、今日私たちは、
doctor tell you
医者はあなたに言います
You have an infection and you need antibiotics
感染症にかかっているので抗生物質が必要です
you have to eat for a week
一週間食べなければなりません
most people say
ほとんどの人が言う
I'll be fine in two or three days
２、３日もすれば治るよ
to help him with the refrigerator
彼の冷蔵庫を手伝うために
next time
下一次
It can also be used when the infection is perfect
感染が完璧な場合にも使用できます
No need to go to the doctor twice
二度医者に行く必要はありません
too wasteful
太浪費
that or
それか
sometimes you have side effects
時々副作用がある
When taking antibiotics
抗生物質を服用するとき
because you put your gut
腸を置くから
All intentions killed him
あらゆる意図が彼を殺した
you made him have diarrhea
あなたは彼を下痢にさせました
you develop other symptoms
他の症状が現れる
you are a doctor
あなたは医者だ
Then put the medicine back and stop
それから薬を元に戻して止めます
It turned out
判明しました
have forgotten
忘れました
then it is not normal to use
それなら使うのは普通ではない
that actually increases the bacteria
それは実際に細菌を増やす
chance of survival
生存の可能性
In addition, generally we are on the feed of overtime acceleration
さらに、一般的に私たちは残業の加速をフィードしています
Because sometimes you want high-density farming
場合によっては高密度の農業が必要になるため
For example, you are in this pigsty
たとえば、あなたはこの豚小屋にいる
Rarely able to raise 100 pigs
100頭の豚を育てることはめったにない
But for high yield
しかし、高収量の場合
Suddenly raised 300 pigs
いきなり300頭の豚を飼育
So many creatures together can also get sick
たくさんの生き物が一緒にいると病気になることもあります
So some antibiotics are added to the feed
したがって、いくつかの抗生物質が飼料に追加されます
it will not have bacterial infection
細菌感染はしないでしょう
This is the result of the actual same order
これは実際に同じ注文の結果です
The gray is darker than this bully
灰色はこのいじめっ子より暗いです
It is the result of our use of cephalosporin
これはセファロスポリンの使用の結果です
The white words are found we say drug resistance
薬剤耐性という白い言葉が見つかりました
golden cephalopod antibiotic resistant bacteria
黄金の頭足類の抗生物質耐性菌
You can see that when we increase the amount of antibiotics
抗生物質の量を増やすとそれがわかります
You can see that after a year or two
1～2年経てば分かるよ
resistant bacteria
耐性菌
It will also increase in number
数も増えますよ
In other words, if you increase the amount of antibiotics used,
つまり、抗生物質の使用量を増やすと、
As a result, you have an increased chance of finding resistance
その結果、耐性が見つかる可能性が高くなります
Then you put the amount of antibiotic
それから抗生物質の量を入れます
lower slowly
ゆっくりと下げる
as a result you see
その結果、ご覧のとおり
Antibiotic bacteria are also slowly declining
抗生物質も徐々に減少している
And you rise to he rises to
そしてあなたは立ち上がる、彼も立ち上がる
For example, this is something like
たとえば、これは次のようなものです
half water
半分の水
Say you take antibiotics
抗生物質を飲んでいると言う
Naturally there is Wu Wu's Xiangke
当然、呉呉の項科もいる。
Bacteria will find ways to get at you
細菌はあなたに侵入する方法を見つけます
So the bacteria that can fight you will also increase with him
だからあなたと戦うことができる細菌も彼と一緒に増えるでしょう
It's half water
半分水ですよ
So this life will never end
だからこの人生は決して終わることはない
This lets you understand
これで理解できるようになります
Okay, I'm done thinking about this antibiotic.
さて、この抗生物質について考えるのは終わりました。
we pick up now
今迎えます
to this diet pill
このダイエット薬に
what about diet pills
ダイエット薬はどうですか
our this
私たちのこれ
This we call Anti-Obsert
これがアンチオブサートと呼ばれるものです
Obsert actually means fat
観察とは実際には脂肪を意味します
that is
あれは
i just said
私はちょうど言いました
I mean we have obesity
つまり肥満があるということです
Of course it doesn't pose any threat to us
もちろんそれは私たちにとって何の脅威にもなりません
Of course everyone wants to say
もちろん誰もが言いたいこと
There is no TV in this day and age
このご時世にテレビはない
everyone says
誰もが言う
I won't tell you how skinny this girl is
この女の子がどれほど痩せているかは教えません
Multiple aiming bars
複数の照準バー
how fat is this girl
この女の子はどれくらい太っていますか
How big is her size
彼女のサイズはどのくらいですか
impossible
不可能
So generally speaking, if you carry a little
一般的に言えば、ちょっとしたものを持ち運ぶ場合、
If you can't do it with diet and exercise
食事と運動で改善できない場合
Then we have to use drugs
それなら麻薬を使わなければならない
General weight-loss drugs probably cannot escape from these three functions
一般的な減量薬ではおそらくこの3つの機能から逃れることはできないでしょう。
This drug directly reduces your appetite
この薬は食欲を直接低下させます
Make you not want to eat and make you feel full all the time
食べたくない気分にさせ、常に満腹感を与えます
Otherwise it's altering your rookie's ability to metabolize
そうしないと、新人の代謝能力が変わってしまいます。
It means to let you, a newcomer, metabolize
新人のあなたに新陳代謝をさせるという意味です
It was originally you, for example, after we are middle-aged
元々は君だった 例えば僕らが中年になってから
If the newcomer's metabolism becomes low
新人の代謝が低下すると
It is very likely that after eating, everything will be easily tired in the body.
食後は体が疲れやすくなっている可能性が高いです。
Increase the rate of your newcomer's metabolism
新人の新陳代謝率を高める
or what you ate today
または今日食べたもの
If you don't absorb it, you won't let it out
吸収しないと外に出さない
so change your appetite
だから食欲を変えてください
Otherwise it is to increase the rate of your newcomer's metabolism
それ以外の場合は、新人の代謝率を高めることです
Otherwise, what you eat will not be absorbed
そうしないと、食べたものが吸収されません
these three
この3つ
so we say diet pills
だからダイエット丸薬って言うんです
Also known as We lost drop
ドロップを失ったとしても知られています
just let you eat
ただ食べさせてください
sorry, drugs that make you lose weight
ごめんなさい、痩せる薬です
Usually, you diet pills
通常、ダイエット薬は
There will be instructions on it that say
そこには次のような指示があります
I hope you can keep your diet balanced and exercise
バランスの取れた食事と運動を心がけていただければと思います
he knows hope
彼は希望を知っている
If your medicine is no joke, don't sue him
あなたの薬が冗談じゃないなら、彼を訴えるな
Because do you have to pay attention to diet?
食事に気をつけないといけないから？
Are you really exercising?
本当に運動してますか？
If you don't do it, you can't sue him if he can do it
あなたがそれをしなければ、彼がそれをできるのなら、あなたは彼を訴えることはできません
There are currently two drugs
現在2種類の薬があります
a Zenicle
ゼニクル
That one is called Redactyl
あれはリダクチルと呼ばれるものです
Then we call it screw fairy in Chinese
中国語ではネジ妖精と呼びます
then to make you cool
それからあなたをクールにするために
Then there's Redactyl's falling beauty
それからリダクティルの落ちていく美しさ
that you know
あなたが知っていること
The business of our drug is actually the same as the general one
当社の医薬品の事業内容は、実は一般の医薬品と同じです。
why?
なぜ？
Look at this Zenicle
このゼニクルを見てください
It's called screw fairy
ネジ妖精といいます
But our troublesome Laninq in Taiwan
でも、台湾の厄介なラニンク
Because of the name Zenicle
ゼニクルという名前のせいで
You see it makes you cool, because it's cool to lose weight
わかるでしょう、痩せることはクールだからです
so what
だから何
So I think the name of our Taiwan class
それで、私たちの台湾クラスの名前だと思います
Because this term is only used in Taiwan
この言葉は台湾だけで使われている言葉なので、
If you are in the general South China area, you still use the screw fairy
一般的な華南エリアにお住まいの場合は、まだネジ妖精を使用しています
that in addition
それに加えて
Luo Meiting
ルオ・メイティン
You have to speak Taiwanese, Luo Weiting
台湾語を話さなければなりません、ルオ・ウェイティン
If you eat your weight, you will lose weight
自分の体重を食べたらロー・ウェイティングになるよ
This English is also very good
この英語もとても上手です
Cause R-E-D-U-O-R-E-D-U-O
因為R-E-D-U-O-R-E-D-U-O
It means lowering
下げるという意味です
R-E-D-U-O-R-E-D-U-O
R-E-D-U-O-R-E-D-U-O
So the naming is very interesting
ネーミングがとても面白いですね
This is very knowledgeable
これはとても詳しいですね
Then let's talk about these two drugs to explain to you
それでは、これら 2 つの薬について説明しましょう
this Rochester
このロチェスター
Zenico, as I just mentioned, is a photo of Miku
ゼニコは先ほども言いましたがミクの写真です。
What about the drug?
薬はどうですか？
Rosh
ロシュ
In most countries, he will do business and sales
ほとんどの国で、彼はビジネスと販売を行います
what about this drug
この薬はどうですか
found out
見つけた
they were in
彼らは中にいた
As I said just now, it means that the material is collected from nature.
先ほども言いましたように、自然の中から採取したものということになります。
So he's in this kind of coal smelter
だから彼はこんな石炭精錬所にいるんだ
Deposited Drugs
寄託された薬物
Then you will see that this is the stored medicine
すると、これが保管されている薬であることがわかります。
Then this is the main ingredient of our later Zenico
これが後のZenicoの主成分です
Then you'll see that the complete difference is
そうすれば、完全な違いは次のとおりであることがわかります。
This looks like it has two swords on it
これは双剣を持っているように見えます
But generally speaking, this kind of double sword
しかし、一般的に言えば、この種の双剣は
will be more unstable
より不安定になります
So they decided he reduced it to a saturated carbon chain
そこで彼らは、それを飽和炭素鎖に還元したと判断した
so this is later
だからこれは後ほど
Later, the more stable version is used in this Zeniko
その後、より安定したバージョンがこの Zeniko で使用されます。
The main cost of this screw room
このネジ部屋の主な費用
what is it for
それはなんのためですか
How does it work?
どのように機能するのでしょうか?
What they found was against us in Congyizang
彼らが発見したのは、孔義蔵で私たちに敵対するものでした
The Lipase secreted by Chris Yizang
クリス・イーザンが分泌するリパーゼ
Is it the breakdown of fat?
脂肪の分解ですか？
In other words, we usually eat mushrooms in the food
つまり、私たちは普段、キノコを食べ物に入れて食べているのです。
start to be broken down in the digestive tract
消化管で分解され始める
What if it's fat
太ったらどうしよう
what about this time
今回はどうですか
Usually need this lipolysis does not work
通常、これが必要な脂肪分解は機能しません
It becomes small molecules of fat that will be absorbed by Xiaochang
脂肪の小さな分子となり、Xiaochang に吸収されます。
What if at this time
この時だったらどうしよう
you added drugs
あなたは麻薬を追加しました
Can put this Lipase
このリパーゼを入れることができます
Suppress this N-RAN
この N-RAN を抑制する
This N-RAN has no way to work
この N-RAN には機能する方法がありません
So you'll find that says
つまり、次のことがわかります
the fat you eat
あなたが食べる脂肪
it won't be broken down
それは壊れません
will not be absorbed
吸収されません
will be drained
排出されます
so what are its side effects
それで、その副作用は何ですか
just drain oil
油を抜くだけ
sorry press too fast
ごめんなさい、早く押しすぎました
will drain oil
油を排出します
So the main side effect of this screw room
このねじ部屋の主な副作用は
everybody knows
誰もが知っている
if you have eaten
食べてしまったら
you will know say
あなたは言うことを知っているでしょう
it causes disturbances in your intestines
腸内に障害を引き起こす
Then to the part that will let you pull the oil out
続いてオイルを抜く部分へ
Then I have friends who have eaten Ross Union
それから、ロスユニオンで食事をした友達がいます
I haven't eaten
食べていない
Although my weight is not very standard
私の体重はあまり標準ではありませんが、
but that is to say
しかし、それはつまり
I've heard that he sometimes
時々彼はいると聞いたことがあります
It's just that you have to eat too normally
ただ、普通に食べすぎるとダメですよ
Just follow the kitchen to eat
キッチンに従って食事をするだけです
you won't be able to get in
あなたは入ることができなくなります
will run up your pants
パンツを駆け上がるだろう
Because that oil is still too fast
あのオイルはまだ速すぎるから
because usually we say sorry
だって普通は「ごめんなさい」って言うから
I'm talking nasty
意地悪なこと言ってるよ
Let's defecate is going piece by piece
一人ずつ排便しましょう
that will be slower
それは遅くなります
But because it was oily at that time
でもその時は油っぽかったので
So these substances will be discharged very smoothly
したがって、これらの物質は非常にスムーズに排出されます
so sometimes you don't
だから時々そうしないこともある
No it's a side effect of a Manzao
いや、マンザオの副作用だよ
But it's okay
しかし、それは大丈夫です
That's because compared to the next words
それは次の言葉と比べて
he is very good
彼はとても良いです
Rowe Hall
ロウ・ホール
What about the Rowe Hall?
ロウ・ホールはどうですか？
it's mostly about being aware of your appetite
それは主に自分の食欲を意識することです
Then this problem will be more
そうなるとこの問題はさらに大きくなる
why
なぜ
Because it is mainly to target your
それは主にあなたのことをターゲットにするためです
Because there are some hormones in our body
私たちの体内にはホルモンが存在するため、
normal here
ここでは普通です
The reaction is really
その反応は本当に
For example, our kidney adenoids
たとえば、腎臓のアデノイド
and this
この
Sterotonic it turns golden amine
ステロトニック それは黄金のアミンに変わります
Or Dopamine Dopaamine
あるいはドーパミン ドーパミン
These things are neurotransmitters
これらは神経伝達物質です
that's in the body
それは体の中にある
Its quantity is strictly controlled
その量は厳密に管理されています
then these should
そうすれば、これらは
these are
これらは
The main function of this Luo Meiting is
このLuo Meitingの主な機能は次のとおりです。
When these neurotransmitters
これらの神経伝達物質が
it recycles
それはリサイクルします
when recycle
リサイクルするとき
it holds it back
それはそれを抑制します
So it turns into saying there are too many of these substances
つまり、これらの物質が多すぎるということになります
so you can imagine
想像できるように
The result of having too many of these neurotransmitters
これらの神経伝達物質が多すぎることの結果
is to become
になることです
You become very hyper
とてもハイパーになります
you can't get in
入ることはできません
What about the result that you can't get in?
入らないという結果はどうなるのでしょうか？
Of course the first one will increase your sense of security
もちろん最初のほうが安心感が高まります
But what?
でも何？
its main problem
その主な問題
yes you will have a lot of problems
はい、たくさんの問題が起こるでしょう
your heart beats faster
あなたの心臓の鼓動が速くなります
blood pressure rise
血圧上昇
because you can't get in
入れないから
Then the half tongue is your dry mouth
そうすると舌の半分が口の渇きになります
then bored with insomnia
それから不眠症にうんざりしました
Of course you're tired of death and insomnia
もちろん、あなたは死と不眠症にうんざりしています
people will lose weight
人々は体重を減らすでしょう
But its problem is
しかし、その問題は
will let you
させていただきます
your whole life
あなたの人生全体を
make your life happy
あなたの人生を幸せにする
will be completely insomnia
完全に不眠症になります
That is to say, in comparison with Luo Shixian just mentioned
つまり、先ほど述べた羅世仙と比較すると、
this will be more serious
これはもっと深刻になるだろう
because it just regulates your hormones
ホルモンを調節するだけだから
or regulate your neurotransmitters
または神経伝達物質を調節する
This is more serious
これはもっと深刻です
In front of Luo Shixian, he asked you to guide him.
羅世仙の前で、彼はあなたに案内してほしいと頼みました。
Take a shower, you can use as much oil as possible
シャワーを浴びて、できるだけ多くのオイルを使用できます
In case it is wearing two pants
パンツを2枚履く場合
three is ok
3つで大丈夫です
That's the one that directly affects your daily life.
それはあなたの日常生活に直接影響を与えるものです。
that would be quite troublesome
それはかなり面倒だろう
Then they also found out that
その後、彼らも次のことを知りました。
because some people ate
食べてる人もいたから
some cardiovascular diseases
いくつかの心血管疾患
so what
だから何
US Food and Drug Administration
米国食品医薬品局
FDA
FDA
It is food and drug administration
食品医薬品局です
Funding Pharmacology Continental Doctors
薬理学コンチネンタルドクターへの資金提供
because of the many reports
たくさんの報告があるので
So they were last year in 2001
それで彼らは去年の2001年でした
He just said he had a limit
彼はただ限界があると言いました
That is, people over the age of 65
つまり65歳以上の人
be careful when eating
食べるときに注意してください
That's because of a lot of bad reports
悪い報告が多いからだよ
because of many side effects
多くの副作用があるため
So Abe Pharmaceuticals in
そこで安倍製薬は、
Because he had a warning from the FDA in August
8月にFDAから警告を受けていたため
He will do his best in time
彼は時間内に最善を尽くすだろう
Removed from the U.S. market
米国市場から削除されました
Because this will lead to a lot of legal litigation issues
これは多くの法的訴訟問題につながるため、
they can't afford it
彼らにはそれを買う余裕がない
So at the moment, although the silver quality sounds good
現時点では、シルバーの品質は良いように聞こえますが、
Loviting
愛情深い
But the problem is that his stock price may be as low as Lo Weiting
しかし問題は、彼の株価がロー・ウェイティングと同じくらい低いかもしれないということだ
So he finally had to quit
それで彼は最終的に辞めなければならなかった
Therefore, currently available diet pills
したがって、現在入手可能なダイエット薬は、
And it's safer that Mr. Ross
そして、ロスさんのほうが安全です。
The next three to ask us are Welcom
次に私たちに尋ねる 3 人は Welcome です
He Wergon's this
彼はワーゴンです、これは
Drug development is also very interesting
創薬も面白いですね
Of course Wei Ergang, of course everyone, as the name suggests
もちろん魏爾剛も、もちろん全員もその名の通り
That is, he would tell us to make up for the dysfunction
つまり、機能不全を補えと言うのです。
then why
それでなんで
Because in fact, it didn’t mean that we must develop this
実際、これを開発しなければならないという意味ではなかったので、
Because I don't think pharmaceutical companies will develop this specifically
製薬会社がこれを特別に開発するとは思えないので
No one has ever developed this sexual function before their disorder
病気になる前にこの性機能を発達させた人は誰もいません
He's actually mostly at that Pfizer factory.
実際、彼はほとんどファイザーの工場にいます。
Their lab over here in the UK
ここ英国にある彼らの研究室
They want this one for high blood pressure and heart and foot pain
彼らは高血圧や心臓や足の痛みにこれを望んでいます
diseases for drug development
創薬のための病気
Everyone knows
みんな知ってる
Our blood pressure is regulated in many different ways
私たちの血圧はさまざまな方法で調節されています
one of them is
そのうちの1人は
due to constriction of blood vessels
血管の収縮により
It directly affects blood pressure
血圧に直接影響する
It's like today if a water pipe
水道管なら今日みたい
You press hard on your water pipe
水道管を強く押すと
Of course the water pressure changes
もちろん水圧も変わります
If the material of this water pipe
この水道管の材質なら
To loosen or loosen the material
素材を緩めたり緩めたりするには
the blood pressure will get worse
血圧が悪化するでしょう
So the idea was to say
そこでアイデアはこう言うことでした
if i could develop a drug
薬を開発できたら
relax the muscles of the blood vessels
血管の筋肉を弛緩させる
lower blood pressure
血圧が下がります
So they hoped to say
そこで彼らはこう言いたかったのです
Using the contraction or relaxation of this vascular muscle
この血管筋の収縮や弛緩を利用して
To treat high blood pressure and new foot pain
高血圧と新たな足の痛みの治療に
Unexpectedly, it failed during the human experiment
人体実験でまさかの失敗
As a result, you will feel that doctors and nurses are very powerful
その結果、医師や看護師の存在が非常に強いと感じるようになります。
Although failed
失敗したけど
But he noticed that
しかし彼はそれに気づいた
Every one of these infectious patients will have thin gas
これらの感染症患者は皆、薄いガスを持っているでしょう
Of course, if the nurse sees what he thinks
もちろん看護師が見たらどう思うか
maybe because i'm pretty
たぶん私はきれいだから
Then this sushi patient reacted to me
するとこの寿司患者が私に反応した
of course he is happy
もちろん彼は幸せです
But this nurse I think he's the same as Felan
でもこの看護師はフェランと同じだと思う
also very careful
也非常小心
He noticed that I might not look good
彼は私の見た目が良くないかもしれないことに気づいた
Why every patient sees me like this
なぜすべての患者が私をそのように見るのか
So he went to report to Fighter
それで彼はファイターに報告に行きました
Fighter must say this is a good thing
ファイターはこれが良いことだと言うに違いない
So let's just not do that clinical test for high blood pressure.
ですから、高血圧の臨床検査はやめましょう。
let's try
やってみよう
Is it possible to win the above question?
上記の質問に勝つことは可能でしょうか？
because it's the same
それは同じだから
These are also blood vessels to increase his blood flow
これらは血流を増やすための血管でもあります
So his blood flow on the air mass side can increase
そのため、気団側の血流が増加する可能性があります
Just Arrive
ちょうど到着
so what about the drug
それで薬はどうですか
It's a drug that looks like this
こんな感じの薬です
We think Syndana Fuel
シンダナ燃料だと思います
The most important thing I just said is
今言った最も重要なことは、
We control the relaxation of blood vessels
血管の弛緩をコントロールします
called Psychogenp
サイコジェンプと呼ばれる
Psychogenp mainly controls the drooping of blood vessels
Psychogenpは主に血管の垂れ下がりを制御します
Then this Psychogenp has a decomposed effect number
そして、このPsychogenpは分解された効果番号を持っています
called PdE5
PdE5と呼ばれる
This is called Fastal Diasdase
これはファスタールジアスダーゼと呼ばれます
That is to say
つまり
PsychoGNV breaks it down
PsychoGNV がそれを解明する
Then they found
それから彼らは見つけました
This Vahua this drug molecule
このヴァーフア、この薬物分子
to inhibit its decomposition effect
その分解作用を抑制する
just make it indestructible
ただ破壊不可能にするだけ
So it became more and more like this PsychoGNV
どんどんこうなっていったPsychoGNV
So this PsychoGNV has been regulating
つまり、このPsychoGNVが規制しているのです
Let this blood vessel relax and relax
この血管をリラックスさせてリラックスさせてください
So it means that the blood flow keeps increasing
つまり血流が増え続けるということです
That's certainly possible for the blood vessels of the heart
心臓の血管なら確かにその可能性はある
Because it may be relatively thick, it may be difficult to get the effect
比較的厚みがあるため、効果が得られにくい場合があります
But for the sexual organs, I think it's just right
でも性器に関してはそれがちょうどいいと思う
just happened to come across
たまたま出会っただけ
to relax the blood vessels
血管を弛緩させる
then get engorged
それから充血する
That's because of the result
それは結果だから
These three can get Nobel Prize
この3人はノーベル賞取れるかも
But he didn't find Wei Erjiang
しかし魏爾江は見つからなかった
don't know don't get me wrong
分かりません、誤解しないでください
Because finding Verjan is
なぜなら、ベルジャンを見つけることは、
There are dozens and Werjiang
数十とウェイルジャンがあります
Then why did they win the Nobel Prize?
では、なぜ彼らはノーベル賞を受賞したのでしょうか？
Because I just talked about this PsychoGNV
ちょうどこのPsychoGNVについて話したばかりなので
it's a physiological process
それは生理学的プロセスです
In fact we found that
実際、私たちはそれを発見しました
Nitrogen Oxide
窒素酸化物
There is this small molecule Nitrogen Oxide
この小さな分子の窒素酸化物があります
it actually goes to our message
それは実際に私たちのメッセージに送られます
This clause has a great function
この条項には素晴らしい機能があります
Then the last game is because of the discovery
そして最後のゲームは発見のおかげです
Same as Nature Outside
外の自然と同じ
seems to be about the whole biological process
生物学的プロセス全体に関するもののようです
of course
もちろん
Of course, in addition to this new board
もちろん、この新基板に加えて
It is also related to the Biohagra we just talked about
先ほどのバイオハグラにも関係してきますが、
So they got the Nobel Prize in 1998
それで彼らは1998年にノーベル賞を受賞しました
well that
まあそれは
What about this Biohagra?
このバイオハグラはどうでしょうか？
let me tell you
言っておくけど
Although it was discovered by accident
偶然発見されたとはいえ、
But it made Pfizer very profitable
しかし、それによりファイザーは非常に利益を上げました
FDA passed it in 1998 and it can be sold
FDAは1998年にそれを通過させ、販売できるようになりました
Then you see it was only two years around 2000
そうすると、2000 年頃はわずか 2 年間だったことがわかります。
Its deferred sales have reached 1 billion US dollars
繰延売上高は10億米ドルに達した
a B chain
Bチェーン
That is equivalent to about ten billion Taiwan dollars.
これは約100億台湾ドルに相当します。
Then what
じゃあ何
How about in 2000?
2000年はどうでしょうか？
Vagra is the whole
Vagraは全体です
We say that in the global market
世界市場ではそう言います
sexual dysfunction
性機能障害
it accounts for 92%
92%を占めます
But from 2000 to 2007, great changes
しかし、2000 年から 2007 年にかけて大きな変化が起こりました。
what about this time
今回はどうですか
I also just saw its sales drop by more than half
売上も半分以下に落ちたのを見たばかりです
why
なぜ
time for its success tax
成功税の時期
Other pharmacies later joined the development
その後、他の薬局も開発に参加しました
So this one called Celis's Cd4
これは Celis の CD4 と呼ばれるものです
with another drug
別の薬で
I don't know what the Chinese name is called Leventral
レベントラルという中国名は分かりません
These two drugs come to share this market
これら 2 つの薬がこの市場を共有するようになる
so he
彼は
and then what else
それから他に何か
Everyone knows this little blue ball
誰もがこの小さな青いボールを知っています
so in many countries
だから多くの国で
There are some for the production of medicine
医薬品の製造用のものもあります
so what
だから何
his
他的
Then another question he has is
それから彼が抱いているもう一つの質問は、
He's fat
彼は太っている
He is asking us to stuff a fat
彼は私たちに脂肪を詰めるように頼んでいる
because you know
あなたは知っているから
already this medicine
もうこの薬
certainly
そうです
because it is hope
それは希望だから
This drug our trust can
私たちが信頼するこの薬は、
he will
彼は
against this other aspect of the vessel
容器のこの別の側面に対して
So there are also reports that
という報告もありますので、
Also has an effect on neovascular disease
血管新生疾患にも効果がある
that's the pair of eyes
それは目です
because there are some
いくつかあるので
For example, patients with diabetes mellitus
例えば、糖尿病の患者さん
his this
彼のこれ
ah
ああ
That blood vessel in the retina is very fragile
網膜の血管はとても脆いのです
Then if you let him bleed
それで彼に血を流したら
If your eyes bleed
目から血が出たら
often easily blind
しばしば失明しやすい
So these stuffed
それで、これらの詰め物は
so let everyone
だからみんなもそうしましょう
for this
このため
Let the doctor take the medicine
医者に薬を飲ませてください
he will be more cautious
彼はもっと慎重になるだろう
will be replaced by other
他のものに置き換えられます
After talking about weight-loss pills and life-enhancing pills,
減量薬と寿命を延ばす薬について話した後、
Let's talk about cancer drugs first
まずは抗がん剤について話しましょう
There are several anticancer drugs
抗がん剤はいくつかありますが、
The five types I use here
今回使用した5種類
I just want to tell you
ただあなたに言いたいのは
In fact, the research and development of anticancer drugs has actually been going on for decades.
実は、抗がん剤の研究開発は何十年も前から行われているのです。
R&D at the time was actually relatively non-selective
当時の研究開発は実際には比較的非選択的でした
Which means it's probably just cancer cells
ということは、ただの癌細胞かもしれない
it grows faster than this cell
この細胞よりも早く成長する
if we say we kill
私たちが殺すと言ったら
The cancer cells will die more
がん細胞はさらに死滅する
So people will talk about comparing non selective
だから人々は非選択的比較について話すでしょう
not selective
選択的ではない
Like this Wufu urinating to avoid illness and Shunbo
このように病気を避けるために排尿するウーフとシュンボ
I'll talk later
後で話します
Then compare selective therapy
次に選択的治療を比較します
San Zhun
サンジュン
Iris or Estin
アイリスとかエスティンとか
Look at this Abosting
これを見てください。
it's called cancer
それは癌と呼ばれています
I'll stop thinking about it for myself
自分で考えるのはやめます
it's fun to name something
何かに名前を付けるのは楽しいです
that said first
それが最初に言った
these two
この二つ
Uracial we call Uracial
ウラシアル、私たちはウラシアルと呼んでいます
We call this symbol Fo
この記号を Fo と呼びます
This is a chemical therapy
これは化学療法です
Basically it's just like normal Uracial
基本的には通常のウラシアルと同じです
The molecule of uridine is missing a Fo
ウリジンの分子には Fo がありません
Because usually we speak chemically
通常、私たちは化学的に話しますので、
The size of this Fo floating fat
このFo浮遊脂肪の大きさ
It's the same size as our pro
プロと同じサイズです
So if here
それでここなら
if you take it as a waist
腰として捉えると
may trick the enzymes on the body
体内の酵素を欺く可能性がある
So this person means
つまり、この人が意味するのは、
It is basically the same as our natural medicine
基本的には私たちの自然療法と同じです
So this was used very early
つまり、これは非常に早くから使用されていました
Chemotherapy used 40 years ago
40年前に使用された化学療法
very primitive
非常原始
So what I just said is that
それで、私が今言ったことは、
Because IcBioxin is faster
IcBioxinの方が早いから
So it will take more of this medicine
したがって、この薬はさらに必要になります
Then kill IcBioxin
次にIcBioxinを殺します
The main mode of action is to say
主な行動様式は次のとおりです。
When the genetic information of our human body
私たち人間の体の遺伝情報が
When DNA is to be synthesized
DNAを合成するとき
it will not be clear
それは明らかではないでしょう
It thought it was its medicine
それが薬だと思った
just eat it in
ただ食べてください
after eating
食べた後で
It finds that it has no way to make a copy
コピーを作成する方法がないことがわかります
So DNA replication stops
つまりDNAの複製が止まる
The same reason is to say
同じ理由で言うと、
The iC package also has the normal C package
iC パッケージには通常の C パッケージもあります
it's not optional
それはオプションではありません
Just to say that the iC bag will grow faster
iCバッグの成長が早いと言うだけです
Next is SysPlanetine
次はSysPlanetineです
just smooth
ただ滑らかな
why is it called shun
なぜシュンと呼ばれるのか
It is Sys
シスです
Mainly the chemical structure above
主に上記の化学構造
its this
それはこれです
This Lygon of the two
二人のうちのこのライゴン
Compounds are all on the same side
化合物はすべて同じ側にあります
we say Sys
私たちはシスと言います
Shun Bo
シュン・ボー
that's the same
それは同じです
This is in the history of our chemotherapy
これは私たちの化学療法の歴史の中にあります
The first one is very metallic
最初のものは非常にメタリックです
especially if it is very thin
特にそれが非常に薄い場合
i am platinum
私はプラチナです
So this drug should be very expensive
したがって、この薬は非常に高価であるはずです
very valuable
非常に価値のある
and platinum
そしてプラチナ
That
それか
then it mainly can of course
もちろんそれは主に可能です
Can be applied to a variety of cancers
さまざまながんに応用可能
So here's a talk about meat flow
ここで肉の流れについて話します
or a tumor
または腫瘍
or impending cancer
または差し迫った癌
There are knots
節があります
that same
それと同じ
The drug ran into the DNA
薬物がDNAに侵入した
it will happen
それは起こるだろう
What we call ENA
私たちがENAと呼ぶもの
Costing
原価計算
it's called cross join
それはクロス結合と呼ばれます
It's like it's sticky
ベタベタしているような
It's like when DNA replicates
DNAが複製されるときのようなものです
it's the result of it being sticky
それはベタベタした結果です
inhibit the replication of its DNA
DNAの複製を阻害する
So with its genetic message
したがって、その遺伝的メッセージに関しては、
So as a result of this the cell dies easily
その結果、細胞は簡単に死んでしまいます
But his worse result is that he used it for a long time
しかし、彼の最悪の結果は、彼がそれを長期間使用したことです
if you reply
あなたが返信したら
the patient will
患者はそうするだろう
Your tumor will be drug resistant anyway
いずれにしてもあなたの腫瘍は薬剤耐性を持つでしょう
So when this medicine has been used for a while
したがって、この薬をしばらく使用すると、
If unfortunately relapse
残念ながら再発した場合
you have to take other medicine
他の薬を服用しなければなりません
So it looks like it's time for cancer treatment
どうやらガン治療の時期が来たようだ
The doctor should pay close attention
医師は細心の注意を払うべきです
the patient's response to the drug
薬に対する患者の反応
if the reaction is bad
反応が悪い場合
Or when there is drug resistance, change it as soon as possible
または薬剤耐性がある場合は、できるだけ早く変更してください。
Otherwise there is always
それ以外の場合は常に存在します
actually grows very fast
実際には非常に早く成長します
but no time to wait for him
でも彼を待つ時間はない
Those first two are not optional
最初の 2 つはオプションではありません
i just said
私はちょうど言いました
Both normal and cancer cells actually eat it
正常細胞もがん細胞も実際にそれを食べる
But these drugs
しかし、これらの薬は、
is more selective
より選択的です
like paclitaxel
パクリタキセルのような
Taisheng
泰生
called TACSO
タクソーと呼ばれる
you see its tacso
タッソが見えますね
This name is very knowledgeable
この名前は非常に知識豊富です
Why is it called purple triol?
なぜビオラトリオールと呼ばれるのでしょうか？
because mainly in the 60s
主に60年代だから
he found in the pacific
彼は太平洋で見つけた
This is the West Coast of the United States
ここはアメリカの西海岸です
His entertainment is in the United States
彼のエンターテイメントはアメリカにあります
Northern Oregon
北部Oregon
Washington over there
あそこのワシントン
There are many redwood mountains along their coasts
海岸沿いにはセコイアの山がたくさんあります
Redwood Mountain they call Pacific Purple Mountain
彼らはパシフィック・パープル・マウンテンと呼んでいるレッドウッド・マウンテン
Experienced from within his bark
樹皮の中から経験を積んだ
Because of the Pacific Purple Mountain
パシフィック・パープル・マウンテンのせいで
Because the purple mountain that came out was stupid
出てきたジーシャンはバカだから
This drug is actually very famous
実はこの薬はとても有名なんです
Why? Because Zishan is stupid mainly to suppress this
なぜ? 紫山の愚か者は主にこれを抑制するためです。
because when the cell is about to replicate again,
なぜなら、細胞が再び複製しようとするとき、
it will do a wet split
ウェットスプリットを行います
when wet split
濡れて裂けたとき
Sales Galenton start above their casing
Galenton の販売は筐体の上から始まります
It is to make some insect groups on the surrounding pipes
周囲のパイプに虫の群れを作るためです
It is mainly when the worm group around the tube
それは主に、チューブの周りにワームが群がるときです。
hold back in the process
途中で我慢する
So this comparison Selective
したがって、この比較は選択的です
Why? Because the packet splitting will become faster
なぜかというと、パケット分割が速くなるためです。
So if you can suppress this
それでこれを抑えることができれば
The Sambler that surrounds the pipe
パイプを囲むサンブラー
effectively inhibit the cancer cells
がん細胞を効果的に抑制します
This purple mountain idiot is actually very interesting
この紫色の山の馬鹿は実際非常に興味深いです
In the United States, they spent a lot of manpower on the development
アメリカでは開発に多大な労力を費やした
at that time
その時
at this
この時点で
there are some pharmaceutical factories
いくつかの製薬工場があります
they actually do
彼らは実際にそうします
already started to do
すでにやり始めている
measure a little time
少し時間を計る
you have to notice
あなたは気づかなければなりません
This is Supi
スーピです
You can't just cut off all the plain skin on the west coast of the Pacific Ocean
太平洋の西海岸の平らな皮膚をすべて切り取ることはできません
Supi get it Supi
すぴ、わかったすぴ
that is
あれは
because they found out that it might be
彼らはそうかもしれないことがわかったから
Supi may only cure a few diseases
Supi は少数の病気しか治さない可能性がある
So they then went to find some way
そこで彼らは何らかの方法を探しに行きました
able to mass produce this molecule
この分子を大量生産できる
You see this molecule is very complex
この分子は非常に複雑であることがわかります
That just so happens that we are in Taiwan
たまたま私たちは台湾にいます
all 20 years ago
全部20年前
Yong Feng in this company
この会社の永峰
He actually wants to do BioTek
彼は実際に BioTek をやりたいと考えています
I think Wang Shuyuan, if someone has
誰かが持っているなら、王淑源だと思います
should know the process
プロセスを知る必要がある
They sent a professor from Taiwan
台湾から教授を派遣しました
to follow
従う
want to go
行きたい
Get this Technology
このテクノロジーを入手
used to take
取っていた
i don't know how to get it
入手方法がわかりません
but
しかし
just bad luck
ただ運が悪いだけ
Just got caught by the FBI
FBIに捕まったばかりだ
buy line
買一線
Just got caught
たった今捕まった
So they had some legal action at the time
それで彼らは当時何らかの法的措置をとった
so the professor
それで教授は
lived there for a while
しばらくそこに住んでいました
to come back
戻って来て
This is some biotechnology
これはバイオテクノロジーの一種です
Know-how in biotechnology is actually very important
バイオテクノロジーのノウハウは実は非常に重要
Because you originally had to get out of the plain skin
もともと素肌から抜け出す必要があったから
Then how do you go about mass producing this next?
では、次はどうやって量産するのでしょうか？
actually a big problem
実は大きな問題
like we were watching this
私たちがこれを見ていたように
Pan Lin's New Year mass production is the same
潘林の新年大量生産は同じです
That's a very important technology
それはとても重要な技術です
Well then it's IRISA
じゃあイリサだよ
IRIS
虹彩
What about IRISA?
イリサはどうですか？
In fact, the main role is in this
実は、主役はこれです
epithelial growth factor
上皮成長因子
Then this IRISA is actually very famous
で、このIRISAって実はすごく有名なんです
Especially in dealing with this lung cancer
特にこの肺がんの治療においては
Then why is it for
ではなぜそれが目的なのか
We say the receptor for epithelial growth factor
上皮成長因子の受容体と言います
We say we say EGFR
私たちはEGFRと言います
Epidermal
表皮
Gross Factor Receptor
グロスファクター受容体
that means
つまり
In general, many processes in our body
一般に、私たちの体内の多くのプロセスは、
including the replication of its cells
細胞の複製を含む
are subject to this signal
この信号の影響を受ける
inside the signal
信号の中
Let's say it has a message delivery event
メッセージ配信イベントがあるとします。
one of them is
そのうちの1人は
epithelial growth factor
上皮成長因子
That
それか
Ic cell, if it can grow rapidly
Ic細胞、急速に増殖できれば
So his messaging will be very strong
したがって、彼のメッセージは非常に強力になるでしょう
So IRISA is one of the
IRISA もその 1 人です。
It's like a drug
麻薬のようなものだ
which puts a very important message
これは非常に重要なメッセージを伝えます
let him pass the message
彼にメッセージを伝えさせてください
There is no way to transfer smoothly
スムーズに乗り換える方法がない
so beijing says
そう北京は言う
After he inhibited this EGFR
彼がこのEGFRを阻害した後、
After this epidermal growth factor
この上皮成長因子の後に
After acceptor
アクセプタ後
let this cancer cell
このガン細胞を放っておいてください
no way
とんでもない
because he needed information
彼は情報が必要だったので
message received
受信したメッセージ
This cancer cell is able to grow
このがん細胞は増殖することができます
to be able to transfer
転送できるように
Even more severe drug resistance
さらに深刻な薬剤耐性
Then you once you pass this message on the way
その後、途中でこのメッセージを渡すと、
block it later
後でブロックしてください
Cancer cells cannot continue to grow
がん細胞は増殖し続けることができません
continue to transfer
転送を続ける
So this is a
これは
For now
今のところ
Our very effective anti-cancer drug
私たちの非常に効果的な抗がん剤
And then there's Albostin
そしてアルボスチンもいる
This cancer wet court
このガンウェットコート
Then this Albostin and the previous drugs
それから、このアルボスチンと以前の薬
no the same
いいえ同じです
because it is not a drug molecule
薬物分子ではないので
Rather it is a
むしろそれは
What we call a monoclonal antibody
私たちがモノクローナル抗体と呼ぶもの
a big protein
大きなタンパク質
This Humanized Monoclonal Antibody
このヒト化モノクローナル抗体
is a monoclonal antibody
モノクローナル抗体です
then it is mainly
それからそれは主に
We are primarily conscious in our
私たちが主に意識しているのは、
What we call Angiogenesis is angiogenesis
私たちが血管新生と呼ぶものは血管新生です
that is, cancer cells
つまりガン​​細胞です
If it grows fast today
今日も早く成長したら
it has to keep growing
成長し続けなければなりません
or even say it's going somewhere else
あるいは、どこか別の場所に行くとさえ言う
when cancer cells are about to grow
がん細胞が増殖しようとしているとき
Must be a lot of nutrients in the apartment
アパートには栄養がたくさんあるはずです
like a baby growing up
成長する赤ちゃんのように
It must drink milk non-stop every day
毎日休みなく牛乳を飲まなければなりません
cancer cells too
がん細胞も
So it must distinguish some factors
したがって、いくつかの要因を区別する必要があります
Let nearby capillaries escape
近くの毛細血管を逃がす
Then it's like adding the oil pipe in
あとはオイルパイプを追加する感じです
provide it with nutrients
栄養を与えてあげる
We call this process consanguinity
このプロセスを血族関係と呼びます
Angiogenesis is called Angiogenesis
血管新生は血管新生と呼ばれます
that process is very important
そのプロセスはとても重要です
then we are now
それから私たちは今です
They just discovered that using this monoclonal antibody
彼らは、このモノクローナル抗体を使用することを発見しました。
able to put this
これを置くことができます
Regulate the branch of its bloodline generation
その血統世代の分岐を規制する
This process blocks it
このプロセスはそれをブロックします
So it is equal to the cancer wet body, the drug
つまりそれは癌性の濡れた体、薬物に等しい
can make this cancer cell able to
このがん細胞にできるようにすることができます
stop growing up at least
少なくとも成長を止める
So usually it can be used with other chemotherapy
したがって、通常は他の化学療法と併用できます
Then it means that it may allow cancer cells to control the
つまり、がん細胞が制御できる可能性があるということになります。
let it grow
成長させてください
that can be combined with other anticancer drugs
他の抗がん剤と併用できる
let it go on let it die
そのままにしておいて死なせてください
What if the drug is unfortunate?
薬が不幸だったらどうしますか？
Also at the end of last year
昨年末にも
The FDA found that
FDA は次のことを発見しました
This drug is actually for the metastasis of cancer cells
実はこの薬はがん細胞の転移を抑える薬なのです
completely gone
完全になくなった
no obvious curative effect
明らかな治療効果はない
So the FDA said last year
FDAは昨年こう言いました
Abosting is best not used to treat this metastatic cancer
この転移性がんの治療にはアブスティングは使用しないのが最善です
Then of course you can use
もちろん、使用できます
This if cancer cells
これはがん細胞の場合
It can be used if it is swollen cancer
腫れたがんであれば使用可能
but for
しかし、のために
That is, cancers that can metastasize malignantly have no obvious curative effect
つまり、悪性転移する可能性のあるがんには明らかな治療効果がないということです。
A big hit for this company
この会社にとって大ヒット
They target cancer cell metastasis
がん細胞の転移を標的とします
It was found to be inactive
非アクティブであることが判明しました
so cancer wet court
だからガンウェットコート
So cancer shouldn't stop
だから癌は止まらないはずだ
cancer can't stop
癌は止まらない
OK, let's talk about
OK、話しましょう
that's not stethamine
それはステタミンではありません
it's basically this
それは基本的にこれです
we are all a sugar
私たちは皆砂糖です
this sugar
この砂糖
What about glucosamine?
グルコサミンはどうでしょうか？
Basically it's inside our body
基本的には私たちの体の中にあります
Chondroitin
軟骨素
We say chondroitin
コンドロイチンと言います
In which connective tissue are we generally
私たちは一般的にどの結合組織にいるのか
This cartilage between the bone and the heel bone
骨とかかとの骨の間にある軟骨です。
is to make it an important ingredient
それを重要な成分にすることです
so because we say
だから私たちが言うから
Glucosamine is important
グルコサミンは重要です
Say if the bones are bad
骨が悪いなら言ってください
Said that the joints are not good, you need to eat glucosamine
関節の調子が悪いのでグルコサミンを摂る必要があると言われました
Let me tell you about it
それについてお話ししましょう
your
あなたの
that is
あれは
Glucosamine
グルコサミン
It has nothing to do with calcium
カルシウムとか関係ないよ
Because glucosamine it is a
グルコサミンなので、
a monosaccharide molecule
単糖分子
Calcium is a mineral
カルシウムはミネラルです
is something different
何か違うのか
Then everyone knows that is to say
それなら誰もが知っている、つまり
It means that if you eat today
ということは、今日食べたら
Glucosamine
グルコサミン
because it is in our body
それは私たちの体の中にあるので
You are going to synthesize this
これを合成することになります
cartilage time
軟骨時間
it's just a raw material
それは単なる原料です
Raw material only
原材料のみ
so you eat more
だからもっと食べるんだよ
It can make your cartilage grow more
軟骨をさらに成長させることができます
That is to say, it should be outside of your growth rate
つまり、成長率の範囲外にある必要があります
because of U.S
米国のせいで
Generally speaking, patients with joints
一般的に関節のある患者さんは、
we are getting older
私たちは年をとっています
etc.
等
The formation and decomposition of cartilage must be balanced
軟骨の形成と分解はバランスが取れていなければなりません
Therefore, more raw materials must be added
したがって、より多くの原材料を追加する必要があります
Let it grow and decompose a little bit in balance
バランスよく成長し、少しずつ分解していきます。
So we say Prolana is a healthy food
したがって、プロラナは健康食品であると言えます
English is called Dietary Supplement
英語ではDietary Supplementと言います
words also spoken in the United States
アメリカでも使われている言葉
besides vitamins
ビタミン以外にも
except for minerals
ミネラルを除いて
It is one of the most commonly used a health food
健康食品として最もよく使われているものの一つです
The second one is pineapple acid
2つ目はパイナップル酸です
it is also a sugar
それも砂糖です
Bromelain is a monosaccharide
ブロメラインは単糖類です
That pineapple acid is a polysaccharide
パイナップル酸は多糖類です
In fact, this polysaccharide
実はこの多糖類、
It is a regular polysaccharide
普通多糖類です
because its repeating unit is a disaccharide
その繰り返し単位が二糖類であるため、
that one is called what we think
それは私たちが思っているとおりに呼ばれています
gluconic acid
グルコン酸
That's another case of glucose
それはブドウ糖の別のケースです
This is equivalent to a disaccharide
これは二糖類に相当します
Then you see
そうすればわかります
What's interesting about this molecule above is that
上のこの分子の興味深い点は、
it has a lot of skin charge
スキンチャージが多い
So because of the repulsion the malleability of this molecule is very good
反発力のおかげで、この分子の展性は非常に優れています。
And it has a lot of guns that can work with water
そして水を扱うことができる銃がたくさんあります
So what's interesting about this molecule is that it stretches very high
この分子の興味深い点は、非常に高く伸びることです。
will become sticky
ベタベタになります
In addition, its water and ability are very good
また、その水と能力は非常に優れています
so moisturizing
とても保湿力があります
So it is equal to the pot why uric acid is often used in cosmetics
ではなぜ尿酸が化粧品によく使われるのかというとポットに相当します。
There is nothing wrong with the effect of moisturizing
保湿効果には問題ありません
ad didn't lie to you
広告はあなたに嘘をつきませんでした
Then I just said that these pots of uric acid are also present in our body.
次に、これらの尿酸のポットは私たちの体内にも存在すると言いました。
That's usually used in our energy-saving organizations
これは通常、私たちの省エネ組織で使用されています
There is also so much uric acid on the epidermis and nerve tissue
表皮や神経組織にも多量の尿酸が存在します
That's about a normal person weighing 70 kg
これは体重70kgの普通の人に相当します。
About 15 grams of pot uric acid
ポット尿酸約15グラム
That in pot uric acid supremacy is currently recognized
ポット尿酸至上性は現在認識されています
I mean, if you say we have joint problems
つまり、私たちには関節の問題があると言うのであれば、
especially the knee
特に膝
You can directly apply the pot of uric acid
尿酸のポットに直接塗布できます
because it is aimed at osteoarthritis patients
変形性関節症患者を対象としているため、
it is there
それはそこにあります
Didn't mention your osteoarthritis patient
変形性関節症の患者については言及しませんでした
There is a problem with uric acid in this cartilage pot
この軟骨ポットには尿酸に問題があります
After the beating, let its substance be
殴打した後、その内容をそのままにしておきます。
don't wear out too fast
あまり早く消耗しないでください
Because this cartilage is
なぜならこの軟骨は、
Numbing agent between bones
骨の間の麻痺剤
If you don't have that substance
その物質が無いなら
direct bone-to-bone contact
骨と骨の直接接触
that's like
それはまるで
have an effect on bone and joint function
骨や関節の機能に影響を与える
That
それか
This is in addition to the treatment of bone and joint function
これは骨や関節の機能の治療に加えて行われます
usually
いつもの
Osteonasic acid can also
オステオナン酸はまた、
I just said that it is used in cosmetics
化粧品に使われているって言ってたけど
And the FDA US Food and Drug Administration in 2003
そして 2003 年の FDA 米国食品医薬品局
he also said
彼も言いました
if we say
私たちが言うなら
If an older person wants to remove wrinkles
高齢者がシワを取りたい場合
Then you can directly administer osteosarcin
その後、オステオサルシンを直接投与できます。
Because just said he has moisturizing
先ほど保湿力があるとおっしゃっていたので
It's good to keep his ductility
彼の柔軟性を保つのは良いことだ
So it is equivalent to filling wrinkles
つまりシワを埋めるのと同じです
Facial wrinkle
顔のしわ
So this is
それで、これは
his output is very large
彼の成果は非常に大きい
that you know
あなたが知っていること
Osteonasic acid
オステオナン酸
inside to grow
内側で成長するために
Because it is the organ that allows the attack to contain
攻撃を封じ込める器官だから
very high
非常高
It just so happens that few people eat organs, right?
たまたま内臓を食べる人が少ないだけですよね？
in often few people
多くの場合少数の人で
so before
だから前に
Osteonasic acid is separated from this organ
オステオナン酸はこの器官から分離されます
that now yields
それが今では得られます
too much demand
需要が多すぎる
So there are other ways to do production
したがって、他の生産方法もあります
Okay, that's over. Just now.
はい、終わりました。今だけです。
Our weight loss pills, I also just talked about other than health products
私たちの減量薬、健康製品以外についてもお話しました
Let's talk about painkillers now
今度は鎮痛剤について話しましょう
There is also a very interesting story in the painkiller
鎮痛剤にも非常に興味深い話があります
For example, we will talk about R-Spinning, how to find
たとえば、R-Spinning について説明します。
What additional benefits does it have
さらにどのようなメリットがあるのか
it has some disadvantages
いくつかの欠点があります
But what we're going to talk about here is
しかし、私たちがここで話そうとしているのは、
Other than R-Spinning
Rスピニング以外
Now you see in your daily life
今、日常生活の中で目にするのは、
For example, this is called this place
たとえば、ここはこの場所と呼ばれます
In fact, it is Pronatex
実はプロナテックスなんです
You saw in the report a few days ago that
数日前のレポートでご存知のとおり、
Children who eat too much Puna pain will affect their health
プナペインを食べすぎる子供は健康に影響を与える
This is Puna pain
これがプナ痛です
Then there is IP-Profan
次に、IP-Profan です。
In addition, we will talk about some Costone
さらに、コストーンについてもお話します。
What is Costone, people will listen to you to explain
コストーンとは何ですか、人々はあなたの説明に耳を傾けます
R-Spinning is also an old drug
R-スピニングも古い薬です
in fact its history
実際その歴史
was launched in 1899
1899年に発売されました
The pan energy that I talked about at the beginning of today will last longer
今日の初めに話した鍋のエネルギーが長続きします
that aspirin
そのアスピリン
That's because it's a direct translation of aspirin
アスピリンの直訳だから
Then his official name is
そうすると、彼の正式な名前は、
acetylcytocacyl
アセチルサイトカシル
So you guys are saying this is a
それで皆さんは、これは
Acetylated salicylic acid
アセチル化サリチル酸
if this point
この点であれば
If it's not here, it's a salicylic acid
ここにない場合はサリチル酸です
usually we say
通常私たちは言います
This drug has three types
この薬には3種類あります
Why is this medicine so good?
なぜこの薬はそんなに良いのでしょうか？
because it has many good activities
良いアクティビティがたくさんあるので
first it can relieve pain
まず痛みを和らげることができます
it's antipyretic it's anti-inflammatory
解熱作用がある、抗炎症作用がある
Then we'll explain why it
それではその理由を説明します
There will also be this
これもあるだろう
That is to say, an inflammatory reaction process of the body
つまり、体の炎症反応プロセス
Notifies you when your body is emotional
身体が感情的になったときに通知します
So tell the body it will take the body temperature
だから体温を測るよと体に伝えてください
slightly higher
やや高いです
let your body react
体を反応させてみましょう
will get faster
速くなります
That's because of your excessive inflammation.
それは過剰な炎症が原因です。
make your body look like it's not
あなたの体をそうでないように見せる
So you must take this spoonful of medicine
だからあなたはこのスプーン一杯の薬を飲まなければなりません
play out the process
プロセスを実行する
That history is very long
その歴史はとても長いです
because it was in BC
紀元前だったから
three or four hundred years ago
三百年か四百年前
there is such a record
そんな記録がある
Why because at the time they made the willow bark
当時は柳の樹皮を使っていたからです。
to experience
体験する
What about the experience from inside the bark?
樹皮の中からの体験はどうでしょうか？
found that it can directly relieve pain
痛みを直接和らげることができることがわかりました
And it can be said to be the pain when I was a child
そしてそれは子供の頃の痛みとも言えます
Pain relief with tree bark extract
樹皮エキスで痛みを軽減
This is the record of the Greeks
これはギリシャ人の記録です
The later record is that until 1875
後の記録は1875年まで
What about the end of the 1970s?
1970年代の終わりについてはどうでしょうか？
They discovered that this salicylic acid
彼らはこのサリチル酸を発見しました
Our name is Sodium Cylite
私たちの名前はナトリウムサイライトです
That's actually the one without the part
それは実際には部品のないものです
It's the acid part.
酸の部分です。
In fact at that time it was using
実際に当時使っていたのは、
As far as the end of 1875 and 1970
1875年末と1970年まで
That's just saying salicylic acid has some side effects
それはサリチル酸には副作用があるということです
we'll get to that later
それについては後で説明します
The fact that the invention in Aspirin was actually made by this man
アスピリンの発明が実際にこの男によって行われたという事実
is in Bayer Germany
ドイツのバイエルにあります
The basis of their chemistry in Germany is very
ドイツにおける彼らの化学反応の基礎は非常に優れています。
Then their chemist was Felix Hopmann
そして彼らの化学者はフェリックス・ホップマンでした
Well, in fact, his father, because of the joint
そうですね、実際のところ、彼の父親は関節のせいで、
Always eat that salicylic acid
サリチル酸をいつも食べてください
But he complained to his son
しかし彼は息子に文句を言いました
I take this salicylic acid
私はこのサリチル酸を摂取しています
There are often crashes
クラッシュがよくある
And that is waiting
そしてそれが待っています
Our so-called kelp acid is from Lugulin
私たちのいわゆる昆布酸はルグリン産です
some wounds inside the body
本体内部に若干の傷あり
often unpredictable
しばしば予測不可能な
so always with him
だからいつも彼と一緒に
his child
彼の子供
He said you work in a pharmacy
彼はあなたが薬局で働いていると言いました
Then you will do chemistry again
それからまた化学をやります
why doesn't he
なぜ彼はそうしないのか
hold on let me out
ちょっと待って出させて
The results of it
その結果
His son really took acid from this water
彼の息子は本当にこの水から酸を摂取しました
to do all kinds of chemistry
あらゆる種類の化学を行う
did some lalama baba test
ララマババテストをしました
so this is our first
だからこれが私たちの最初の
one in history
歴史上の一つ
human experiment
人体実験
Just try him out
彼を試してみてください
That's a good thing he has good chemistry skills.
彼が優れた化学スキルを持っているのは良いことだ。
they have some
彼らはいくつか持っています
Some
いくつかの
It's the medicine my student made for me
それは私の生徒が私のために作ってくれた薬です
I dare not eat
あえて食べない
Why
なぜ
Then in case there are some impurities
万が一、不純物が入ってしまった場合には
eat it, i'm busy
食べてください、忙しいです
that's the end
それが終わりです
so let his chemistry skills not bad
だから彼の化学のスキルが悪くないようにしましょう
he eats
彼は食べる
turn out
消す
Added this acetylipop
このアセチリポップを追加しました
westernized place
西洋化された場所
the result is very good
結果はとても良いです
so later
だから後で
this pharmaceutical factory
この製薬工場
their beyer company
彼らのバイエル会社
decided to put this
これを置くことにしました
Originally they were producing salicylic acid
もともと彼らはサリチル酸を生産していました
salicylic acid
サリチル酸
This is our ASPY today
今日のASPYです
However, this story has also been overturned
しかし、この話も覆されました
why
なぜ
because at that time they said
なぜならその時彼らはこう言ったからです
Germany was later contested by the Nazis
ドイツはその後ナチスと争った
they were german
彼らはドイツ人でした
because later one
後から一つ
this
これ
Jewish chemist
ユダヤ人の化学者
They said it was his invention
彼らはそれが彼の発明だと言った
It was because the Nazis ruled at that time
当時はナチスが支配していたからだ
He made up a story that
彼はそんな話をでっち上げた
There is a very filial chemist
とても親孝行な化学者がいます
Because he is filial to his father, he will make it
彼は父親孝行だから、必ず成功するだろう
I'm not a historian
私は歴史家ではありません
i can't go
行けません
Say which one is right and both are wrong
どちらが正しくて両方とも間違っていると言う
But the name of Aspirinde is also very famous
しかし、アスピリンデの名前も非常に有名です
A
あ
he's mostly talking
彼はほとんど話している
Because he Westernized this salicylic acid
彼はこのサリチル酸を西洋化したからです
THE SIEGE
包囲戦
S-P-I-R-I-N
S-P-I-R-I-N
this is mainly
これは主に
he was in
彼は中にいた
In this 19th century
この19世紀に
experience from this plant
この植物から得られる経験
the name of the plant
植物の名前
Then there is S-PRIM
次にS-PRIMです。
and this source
そしてこのソース
So I just said 1899
だから私は今 1899 年と言いました
What about Bayer?
バイエルはどうでしょうか？
Just put this on the market
これを市場に出すだけ
That's what they did in 1999 AD
それが西暦1999年に彼らがやったことだ
100 years later they have statistics
100年後、統計が得られる
Currently the most used medicine bowl in the world
現在世界で最も使用されている薬入れ
He seems to have used over a billion medicine bowls
彼は10億個以上の薬入れを使用したようです
Then you'll see this ad from 1923
そうすると、1923 年のこの広告が表示されます。
you see migrant
移民が見えます
The name means neuralgia
名前は神経痛を意味します
this is german
これはドイツ人です
migrant this is arthritis
移民、これは関節炎です
rheumatoid arthritis
関節リウマチ
matoioasuritis
マトイオアスリ炎
You said ASPINE's medicine at that time
あの時はASPINEの薬って言ってたね
Because of this related series Perish
この関連シリーズのため Perish
It is an advertisement of ASPINE in Europe
ヨーロッパのASPINEの広告です
it can be trained to cure bottle headaches
訓練すればボトル頭痛を治すことができる
neuralgia and joint pain
神経痛と関節痛
Why does it have pain relief in ASPINE
ASPINE に鎮痛効果がある理由
Antipyretic and anti-inflammatory
解熱および抗炎症作用
inside our body
私たちの体の中に
To initiate an inflammatory response like this
このような炎症反応を引き起こすには
In fact, it is made of our fat
実はそれは私たちの脂肪から作られています
There is a four double sword
双剣が4本ある
We say Tetraximic Acid
テトラキシム酸と言います
Arachidonic acid
アラキドン酸
It is a twenty carbon fatty acid
炭素数20の脂肪酸です
start here
ここから始める
to do some metabolic reactions
いくつかの代謝反応を行うため
what about here
ここはどうですか
The first very important reaction is the itching reaction
最初の非常に重要な反応はかゆみ反応です
What we call sychroactogenase
シクロアクトゲナーゼと呼ばれるもの
For example, the itching reaction starts
たとえば、かゆみ反応が始まります。
Generate this Perish
この滅びを生成する
Perish we call prostaglandins
滅びを我々はプロスタグランジンと呼ぶ
So why is it called Postagranding
ではなぜポストグランディングと呼ばれるのか
That has nothing to do with the prostate
それは前立腺とは関係ありません
That is to say, this series of reactions of the body
つまり、この一連の身体の反応は、
We call this an inflammatory response
これを炎症反応と呼びます
That just happens to be this Aspirin or what we'll talk about later
それがたまたまこのアスピリンか、後で話すことです。
this other pain medication
この他の鎮痛剤は
are all acting on this Cox
全員がこのコックスに基づいて行動しています
That is to say, this epoxidation enzyme
つまり、このエポキシ化酵素は
Cox1 1 2
コックス1 1 2
so it blocks it
だからそれをブロックする
equal to the following molecules
次の分子に等しい
It's actually all about regulating our inflammatory response.
実際には、炎症反応を制御することがすべてです。
For example, it will be excruciating
たとえば、それは耐え難いことになります
With this, the body temperature can be raised
これで体温を上げることができる
Then what
じゃあ何
Inflammation of these molecules can no longer be produced
これらの分子の炎症はもはや引き起こされません
So it's like shutting it down from the source
つまり、ソースでシャットダウンするようなものです
So we say its main purpose is to control the inflammatory response
したがって、その主な目的は炎症反応を制御することであると言えます。
Mainly this Enzyme
主にこの酵素
That is to say Cox
つまりコックスです
I just mentioned
先ほども言いましたが
it you turn off the principle
あなたが原則をオフにすると
So the latter
それで後者は
prostaglandins
プロスタグランジン
This is not just a single Compound
これは単なる単一の化合物ではありません
Prostaglandin and blood cream
プロスタグランジンと血液クリーム
Dipamine
ジパミン
These molecules are all related to the inflammatory response
これらの分子はすべて炎症反応に関連しています
regulate these physiological responses
これらの生理学的反応を調節する
just turn it all off
すべてをオフにしてください
And the front line counts it's actually a hormone
そして最前線はそれが実際にはホルモンであると考えています
In physiology, it is to transmit the pain sensation to the brain
生理学では、痛みの感覚を脳に伝えることです。
So it's time to say you have a painful inflammatory reaction today
だから今日は痛みを伴う炎症反応があると言う時です
Excessive inflammation makes your physiological response not
過剰な炎症により生理学的反応が鈍くなります。
So you have to use painkillers to shut this source down
したがって、この原因を遮断するには鎮痛剤を使用する必要があります
Then this aspirin is a miracle drug
それならこのアスピリンは奇跡の薬です
So at the time it meant that even though I didn't know anything in 1940
つまり、1940年当時は何も知らなかったとしても、
It is equivalent to listing it in 1899
1899年上場に相当
But his physical
しかし、彼の肉体的
His entire passport is about why he can have such a magical effect
彼のパスポート全体が、なぜ彼がそのような魔法のような効果を発揮できるのかを説明しています。
This perfectly explained until the 1950s by Gang Dan
これは1950年代まではGang Danによって完全に説明されていました。
He clarified this Maconian with his technology
彼はこのマコニアンを技術で解明した
So in 1982 he and two other
それで1982年に彼と他の2人は
I believe they should be Swedish chemistry
スウェーデンの化学であるべきだと思います
Shared Nobel Prize in Physiology or Medicine with Semmelson
センメルソンとノーベル生理学・医学賞を共同受賞
got it in 1982
1982年に入手しました
In addition, aspirin is constantly
さらに、アスピリンは常に服用されています。
because he is a magic molecule
彼は魔法の分子だから
Although Li Tong You Jiu
Li Tong You Jiu ですが
He doesn't just have pain relief
彼は痛みを和らげるだけではありません
he has other
彼には他にもある
most importantly
最も重要なこと
You can avoid it if you don't take low dose aspirin for a day
低用量のアスピリンを1日服用しなければ回避できる
Heavy wind heels
重い風のかかと
Hard Attack
ハードアタック
on the occurrence of cardiovascular disease
心血管疾患の発症について
And they are experimentally confirmed
そしてそれらは実験的に確認されています
Taiwan is relatively rare. If you go to the United States, you will see what they call Low Dose aspirin
台湾は比較的まれですが、アメリカに行くと低用量と呼ばれるアスピリンを目にするでしょう。
Generally, aspirin can be 50 or 80mm
一般に、アスピリンは 50 または 80mm です。
What do we say Primary
初等協会は何を言いますか
Primary prevention is secondary prevention
一次予防は二次予防です
for these people
この人たちのために
He has absolutely no history of cardiovascular disease
彼には心血管疾患の病歴は全くありません
His heart was completely fine before
彼の心は以前は完全に元気だった
They found that he reduced cardiovascular disease by about a tenth
彼らは、彼が心血管疾患を約10分の1減少させたことを発見した
For him, if he has had a stroke and has a background of cardiovascular disease
彼にとって、脳卒中を起こし、心血管疾患の背景がある場合
If he has some cardiovascular disease and myocardial infarction
何らかの心血管疾患や心筋梗塞を患っている場合
If you take low doses of RSP daily
毎日低用量の RSP を摂取する場合
He can also reduce the recurrence rate by 10%
再発率も10%減らすことができる
So this effect is quite significant
したがって、この効果は非常に重要です
So generally speaking, they will recommend you for a day
したがって、一般的に言えば、彼らはあなたに1日を勧めます
Yours can eat about 40 to 80 mini light is enough
ミニは約 40 ～ 80 個食べられるので十分です
can have such a preventive effect
このような予防効果が期待できます
So this is RSP and of course RSP has some problems
これは RSP ですが、もちろん RSP にはいくつかの問題があります
It's just that at the beginning we said that it actually causes some side effects
ただ、最初に、実際には副作用が生じると言いました。
Those side effects include children can not eat
これらの副作用には、子供が食べられないことが含まれます
may cause budding syndrome
可能導致有蕾濕症厚情
RSP he will cause you some itchy problems
RSP 彼はあなたにかゆみの問題を引き起こすでしょう
Although this Hopman he solves his dad's problem
このホップマンは父親の問題を解決します
But in fact, he still has the problem of itching after taking it for a long time.
しかし実際には、長期間服用した後のかゆみの問題がまだ残っています。
Why do people explain
なぜ人は説明するのか
So, they started looking for some other alternative medicine
そこで彼らは他の代替医療を探し始めました
Those alternative medicines include RSP
これらの代替医療には RSP が含まれます
non-inflammatory anti-inflammatory drugs
非炎症性抗炎症薬
We call it NSP
NSPといいます
NSAID
NSAID
so why? because
それでなぜ？なぜなら
Steroid
ステロイド
Just mentioned those Postacans
先ほどポスタカンについて言及しました
Steroid itself
ステロイドそのもの
Steroid itself is an anti-inflammatory drug
ステロイド自体は抗炎症薬です
we say it is
私たちはそうだと言います
But Steroid has serious side effects
しかしステロイドには重大な副作用がある
So what we usually do is a
ですから、私たちが普段やっているのは、
Non-Steroidal Anti-Inflammatory Drugs
非ステロイド性抗炎症薬
on NSAIDs
NSAIDについて
the first one
最初の1つ
It is also famous in history
歴史上でも有名です
Print paper
プリント用紙
就Aslamino fan
アスラミノファン
touch light or
光に触れたり、
Or in the US we call it Tan
またはアメリカではタンと呼びます
Known as Panagl in Taiwan
台湾ではパナグルとして知られています
It's paper
紙だよ
It was on the market in the United States as early as 1953
米国では 1953 年にはすでに販売されていました。
that they now think
彼らは今こう思っている
Because of the fact that it has sold more than RSP
RSPよりも売れているため
And usually we say
そして通常、私たちはこう言います
This is a T token of RSP
RSPのTトークンです
that this
これは
what about the painkiller
鎮痛剤はどうですか
it actually
それは実際に
you can now in
今すぐにできます
available in general medicines
一般医薬品で入手可能
You can buy beyond ingredients
食材以外でも買える
and it works really fast
そしてそれは本当に速く動作します
because after you take
なぜならあなたが取った後だから
It takes about 11 minutes to have an analgesic effect
鎮痛効果が現れるまで約11分かかります
but very good
でもとても良い
and it won't hurt the taste
そして味を損なうことはありません
what about the other
もう一方はどうですか
its something on the upgrade side
それはアップグレード側にあるものです
About one to four hours
1時間～4時間程度
Then I just said that after the 1980s
それから、私は 1980 年代以降について言いました。
Its sales volume has surpassed that of RSP
販売数量はRSPを上回る
So the effect of Pronison is very good
プロニソンの効果は非常に優れています
what about the other
もう一方はどうですか
its
これは
Why was it called Tanel in the first place?
そもそもなぜタネルと呼ばれたのでしょうか？
mainly because they found
主に彼らが見つけたからです
They also Campaign means
キャンペーンの意味もあります
it is small
小さいです
Just talked about RSP
RSPについて話しました
Children are usually not allowed to use
通常、子供は使用できません
so they are
だから彼らは
This is the drug they started giving to the little ones
これは彼らが小さな子供たちに与え始めた薬です
Tanel Children's Extra
タネル・チルドレン・エクストラ
That
それか
I really don't want to talk about its discovery
その発見については本当は話したくないのですが、
time relationship
時間の関係
almost time
ほとんどの時間
I have to speed up a little bit
少しスピードを上げないといけない
What about IP ProFan?
IP ProFan についてはどうですか?
in what we call
私たちが呼んでいるもので
Generally we call it ADV and there is a New Print
一般にADVと呼ばれるもので、ニュープリントがあります。
What about the initial development?
初期の開発についてはどうですか？
Mainly in England there is a science called Steward Eddons
主にイギリスにはスチュワード・エドンズと呼ばれる科学がある
Adams
アダムス
He was looking for a drug
彼は麻薬を探していた
able to treat him with this
これで彼を治療できる
the old one
古いもの
Handover problem
引き継ぎの問題
don't know how to speak english
英語を話す方法がわかりません
that is
あれは
that
それか
hangover problem
二日酔いの問題
Unexpectedly, this medicine turned out to be
思いがけず、この薬は次のようになりました。
No tax but the problem is it can have a painkiller effect
税金はかかりませんが、問題は鎮痛効果があることです
So the effect is also very good
なので効果もとても良いです
Then this is a case of immediate selectivity
これは即時選択性のケースです
In terms of time, I'll jump over first
時間的には私が先に飛び越えます
so-called selective painkillers
いわゆる選択的鎮痛剤
just now
ちょうど今
In our inflammatory response PASS
私たちの炎症反応PASSでは
Cox that NZ
コックス・ザット・ニュージーランド
In fact it comes in two different forms
実際には 2 つの異なる形式があります
We use Cox1, Cox2
Cox1、Cox2を使用します
Cox1 is ubiquitous
Cox1は遍在しています
In fact it can protect you
実際、それはあなたを守ることができます
The inside story of your provocation
あなたの挑発の裏話
so if you hold it back
だからそれを我慢すれば
it has no way to protect
それは守る方法がない
so you get ulcers easily
だから潰瘍ができやすい
So Cox2 is when the inflammatory response
つまり、Cox2 は炎症反応が起こるときです。
will be activated
活性化されます
So usually speaking
だから普通に言うと
We say like R-Speed-In
R-スピードインのように言います
Usually it suppresses both
通常は両方を抑制します
so we are not good
だから私たちは良くない
We say that after taking this medicine
この薬を服用した後はこう言います
Although it can relieve pain
痛みを和らげることはできるものの、
But when reactivating for a long time
しかし、長時間再起動すると、
would be tantamount to destroying your consumption
それはあなたの消費を破壊することに等しい
consume these mucous membranes
これらの粘膜を消費する
is to reactivate
再活性化することです
so it becomes saying
だからこう言うことになる
At that time they thought that
その時彼らはこう思ったのです
Afraid to discover that there are these two different forms
これら 2 つの異なる形式があることを発見するのが怖い
Then my medicine for the next generation
そして私の次世代への薬
Drugs must be suppressed
薬物は抑制されなければならない
Cox2 cannot inhibit Cox1
Cox2はCox1を阻害できない
generally
一般的
but in fact
しかし実際には
There is a problem
問題があります
because
なぜなら
One of the two major pharmaceutical companies in the United States is
米国の 2 つの大手製薬会社のうちの 1 つは、
Merck one is Pfizer
メルクの1つはファイザーです
Bison
バイソン
they went to find the so-called
彼らはいわゆるものを探しに行きました
because I just said I can't
できないと言っただけだから
need
必要
Cox2 to be selective
Cox2 を選択的にする
Doubtful Fox2
ダウトフルフォックス2
It started off fine
順調にスタートしました
Since it was launched in 1999
1999年の発売以来
then the most recent thing
それから最近のこと
But later found out that
しかし、後で知ったのですが、
Why
なぜ
have side effects
副作用がある
Then there's a lot of legal action
そうなったら大規模な法的措置が必要だ
So listed in 1999
ということで1999年に上場
So in 2004 when
それで 2004 年のとき、
Merck had to take him off the shelves automatically
メルク社は彼を棚から自動的に撤去しなければならなかった
That's what people can see
それが人々に見えるものです
2007 before they were taken off the shelves
2007年、店頭から撤去される前
this number may
この数字はもしかしたら
may be a problem
問題があるかもしれない
This number may not be 2007 either
この数字も 2007 年ではない可能性があります
It was in 2001
2001年のことでした
his total
彼の合計
This can be sold for two hundred million dollars every year
これは毎年2億ドルで売れる
so he
彼は
Equal to the history of mankind
人類の歴史と同じ
put this
これを置きます
very large sales
非常に大きな売上
First off
最初に
is this virus
これはウイルスですか
then they have two versions
そうすると、2つのバージョンがあります
pharmaceutical factory is talking
製薬工場が話している
just talking about this world
ただこの世界のことを話しているだけ
did notice this
これに気づきました
The risk of vascular disease
血管疾患のリスク
But our person is the experimental card
でも私達は実験カードです
Of course the manuscript is here
もちろん原稿はここにあります
The patient told the pharmaceutical company that
患者は製薬会社にこう告げた。
You are deliberately concealing your clinical
自分の臨床症状を意図的に隠している
So this is a bit of an argument
これはちょっとした議論です
what about the other one
もう一つはどうですか
It's this gray hot pharmaceutical factory
ここは灰色の製薬工場です
What about his medication?
彼の薬はどうですか？
Must be taken as directed by a physician
医師の指示に従って服用する必要があります
His sales that year turned out to be 3 billion US dollars
その年の彼の売上は30億ドルだったことが判明
Then what I just said
それから私が今言ったこと
After the removal of the Morke drug
モルケ薬の除去後
What about his medicine because it's not off the shelf?
彼の薬は市販品ではないのでどうなるのでしょうか?
so recover slowly
だからゆっくり回復してください
2 billion US dollars by 2006
2006年までに20億米ドル
So there is still some controversy over this drug.
したがって、この薬についてはまだ論争があります。
Because everyone thinks there are still some
まだあるとみんな思ってるから
must be under control
制御下にある必要があります
use under strict supervision
厳重な監督のもとで使用する
i think i'm each for a while
しばらくはそれぞれだと思います
ok let me tell you this
わかりました、これを教えましょう
Killing Bean Wheat
キリングビーンウィート
This drug was developed in the 1950s
この薬は1950年代に開発されました
At that time, he believed that there was a promotional effect
当時は宣伝効果があると信じていた
And for this like a pregnant woman
そしてこれについては妊婦のように
when he has haematological symptoms
血液症状があるとき
He can stop vomiting
彼は嘔吐を止めることができる
So this time is equal to
したがって、この時間は次のようになります
Pregnant women because there is such a magic drug
こんな魔法の薬があるから妊婦さん
Because it has some anti-inflammatory and pain-relieving effects
抗炎症作用や鎮痛作用があるため、
And there will be antiemetic
そして制吐剤もあるだろう
So become a lot of pregnant women
妊婦さんがたくさんなるので
within that time period
その期間内に
That is to say, everyone is equal to
つまり、誰もが平等なのです
Because blood is very
血がとても多いので、
that is to say it is a difficult
つまり難しいです
very uncomfortable symptoms
非常に不快な症状
So it becomes a saying that pregnant women should take it
なので妊婦は摂取すべきと言われています
But the problem was discovered later
しかし問題は後になって判明した
The child's birth deformity
子供の先天的奇形
Look at the soles of this child's feet
この子の足の裏を見てください
Suddenly there is one more beside him
突然彼の隣にもう一人がいる
one toe out
つま先が片方出ている
let you go out and see his other arm
外に出て彼のもう一方の腕を見てみませんか
Only as long as the upper arm
上腕くらいの長さだけ
This severe deformity makes this lethal bean wheat
この重度の変形により、この致命的な豆は小麦になります
in the 1950s
在1950年代
Discontinued in early 1960
1960 年初頭に生産中止
probably in our world
おそらく私たちの世界でも
probably have time
おそらく時間があります
about four or five years
4、5年くらい
But it caused about 10,000 to 20,000
しかし、それは約10,000から20,000を引き起こしました
don't know
わかりません
Model
モデル
right
右
used in the bathroom
浴室で使用されている
Then later in the recent
それから最近では
They found that some tiredness curative effect
彼らはある程度の疲労回復効果を発見した
I can't talk about the time relationship here.
時間の関係についてはここで話すことはできません。
That is to say for some
つまり、一部の人にとっては
symptoms of immunity or leprosy
免疫またはハンセン病の症状
autoimmune disease
自己免疫疾患
it has some healing properties
ある程度の癒し効果がある
Then I won't talk about it here
それならここでは話さないよ
In the end, I talked about some
最後にいくつかお話しましたが、
we just talked about the term new drug development
先ほど新薬開発という言葉について話しました。
What about new drug development?
新薬開発についてはどうですか？
This is to introduce you
ご紹介するのはこれです
We are now developing a drug
私たちは今、薬を開発中です
In fact it is very strict
実はとても厳しいのです
then you have to because
それならそうしなければなりません、なぜなら
we say
私達は言う
Clinical time is considered to be human body
臨床時間を人体として考える
That
それか
very strict
非常に厳しいです
So usually we need to have enough
したがって、通常は十分な量が必要です
This so-called pre-clinical
このいわゆる前臨床
data means clinical trials
データとは臨床試験を意味します
these data
これらのデータ
you have to collect
集めなければなりません
Let's say you want to tell people this
これを人々に伝えたいとします
toxicity of this molecule
この分子の毒性
inside
中身
How are you doing with everyone?
皆さんはいかがお過ごしでしょうか？
To collect enough data
十分なデータを収集するには
You're going to send it to the FDA
FDAに送ってるのね
The audit thinks that this data
監査では、このデータは次のように考えられます。
can be tested in humans
人間でも検査できる
He will follow you to do clinical trials
彼は臨床試験を行うためにあなたをフォローします
This clinical trial actually has three phases
この臨床試験には実際には 3 つのフェーズがあります
Have Face 1 Face 2 Face 3
顔 1 顔 2 顔 3 を持つ
Every stage is checked
各段階でチェックされます
So it's actually a very rigorous process
実際には非常に厳密なプロセスです
you can't say casually
気軽に言うことはできません
You mean I'm like that right now
つまり今の私がそうだということですね
Feed him straight away
すぐに彼に餌をあげてください
it's okay to fuck dad
お父さんとセックスしても大丈夫です
in fact it's fine
実際には大丈夫です
Now after these 100 years
この100年後の今
I think we have a good idea for a process like this
このようなプロセスについては良いアイデアがあると思います
Right Reductive
右還元的
Generally speaking
一般的に言えば
The so-called preclinical experimental data
いわゆる前臨床実験データ
basically because we have to do it before the animals
基本的には動物よりも先にやらなければならないからです
Not to be done before human experiments
人体実験の前にやってはいけないこと
So it's an animal model
つまり動物モデルです
So at this time you have to tell others about the experiment of reading Chinese
したがって、現時点では、中国語を読むという実験について他の人に話さなければなりません
what happens with this drug
この薬で何が起こるのか
we are all metabolized
私たちは皆代謝されています
pharmacokinetics
薬物動態
How does he supplement the various temperatures in the body
体内のさまざまな温度をどのように補っているのか
you have to speak clearly
はっきりと話さなければなりません
inside the animal
動物の中で
can you do it with your heart
心を込めてできますか？
explain clearly
明確に説明する
When it comes to clinical trials, there is a so-called internship
臨床試験に関しては、いわゆるインターンシップがあります。
What about medical internships?
医療インターンシップについてはどうですか？
with healthy people
健康な人たちと
It is a healthy person to do the experiment
実験を行うのは健康な人です
Of course this pre-punctural inoculation
もちろんこの穿刺前接種
made in animals
動物で作られた
Do it again
再びそれを行う
After this is passed
これを過ぎた後は
You can enter the second and third stages
第2ステージ、第3ステージに入ることができます
The second stage, the third stage
第二段階、第三段階
what about this time
今回はどうですか
is used on patients
患者に使用されます
You have to look at him at this time
今度は彼を見なければなりません
Is there any medical effect
医学的な効果はありますか
this is very important
これはとても重要です
And you have to give the doctor in the hospital
そして病院の医師に説明しなければなりません
or you can't talk to him
そうでないと彼と話せない
Which one is the drug and which one is the placebo
どれが薬でどれがプラセボなのか
because you might
なぜならあなたはそうするかもしれないから
A group of patients is given vitamins
患者グループにビタミンが投与される
but you give him medicine
でもあなたは彼に薬を与えます
A group of his patients, that's the real drug in the experiment
彼の患者のグループ、それが実験の本当の薬です。
But doctors and nurses don't know
でも医者も看護師も知らない
so they
ので
It's just that they just go over the table
ただ彼らはテーブルの上を通過するだけです
To collect blood and urine from patients
患者さんから血液や尿を採取するため
Then analyze his symptoms
それから彼の症状を分析してください
Then if you wait until the third stage
じゃあ第三段階まで待てば
it's huge
それは大きいです
Experiments with potentially hundreds or thousands of people
潜在的に数百人または数千人を対象とした実験
At this time, the experiment will be compared with existing drugs
現時点では、実験は既存の薬と比較されます
for comparison
比較用
If there is a significant effect
重大な効果がある場合
he will let
彼はさせてくれる
if no noticeable effect
顕著な効果がない場合
or worse
あるいはさらに悪いことに
Then it is very likely that your previous efforts will be in vain.
そうなると、これまでの努力が無駄になってしまう可能性が非常に高いです。
then if you are lucky
それで運が良ければ
Can you pass these experiments?
あなたはこれらの実験に合格できますか?
You can talk to the US Food and Drug Administration
米国食品医薬品局に相談することができます。
or Taiwan's Food and Drug Administration
または台湾食品医薬品局
Sent all is a New Drug application says
すべて送信されたのは新薬申請書です
I did all the data
データは全部やったよ
I have human experiment data
人体実験データがある
please take a good look
よく見てください
then if you are satisfied
それで満足したら
you let me go public
あなたは私を公にさせてくれました
So it's a very rigorous process
したがって、非常に厳格なプロセスです
That
それか
So it's done like this
それで、このようにできました
Why
なぜ
We say that this internship is more and more
このインターンシップはますます増えていくと言っています
This time is getting longer and longer
この時間がどんどん長くなっていきます
That means you spend more and more money
つまり、どんどんお金を使ってしまうということです
more and more time
越來越多時間
because of us
私たちのせいで
What about the human body?
人間の体はどうでしょうか？
it's too early
まだ早い
So we have to test more things
したがって、より多くのことをテストする必要があります
more and more
だんだん
So it turns into saying you need to pay more and more
だからもっともっとお金を払えということになる
A billion dollars may not have been needed ten years ago
10年前には10億ドルも必要なかったかもしれない
Now it may cost 1.2 to 1.5 billion
今なら12億から15億かかるかもしれない
What about the average statistical average?
統計上の平均値はどうでしょうか?
probably needed before
おそらく以前に必要だった
five to eight years
5年から8年
Then you may have to delay it for ten to twelve years
その場合、10年から12年延期する必要があるかもしれません
So this is getting
これは、
more and more money
ますますお金が増える
An increasingly risky Biannese
ますます危険なビアンネーゼ
In addition, in fact, we are developing
また、実際に開発を行っているのは、
There are some stimulating measures
刺激策もある
like this orphan drug act
この孤児薬法のように
Open drug的Ecusivity
オープンドラッグの執行力
And Face trading
そしてフェイストレード
for some
いくつかのための
rare disease
稀な病気
how exciting
楽しそう
The pharmaceutical company asked him to invest
製薬会社は彼に投資を依頼した
or some medicine
または薬
There are currently no effective treatments
現在有効な治療法はありません
forFace trading
用Face trading
can get quickly
すぐに手に入る
get certified and go public
認定を受けて公開する
so these things i think
だから私はこれらのことを思う
Today I just use a very simple
今日は非常にシンプルなものを使用します
speech to everyone
みんなに向けてのスピーチ
to illustrate
説明する
Then I'll wait a minute. I don't know what's wrong with you.
じゃあ、ちょっと待ってください。何が問題なのか分かりません。
If you have any questions, I hope you can ask them
ご質問がございましたら、ご質問いただければ幸いです
then i will talk about it today
それなら今日はそれについて話します
Well, we thank Professor Lin for his very simple and wonderful speech
リン教授の非常にシンプルで素晴らしいスピーチに感謝します。
many stories
たくさんの物語
20 minutes is not enough, we are open to your questions
20 分では十分ではありません。ご質問をお待ちしております
Come
来て
that you know is my question
それは私の質問です
we don't have much time now let's just talk
今はあまり時間がないのでちょっと話しましょう
the avestin just mentioned
先ほど言及したアベスティン
that thing
その事
My eyes were in 2005
私の目は2005年にあった
that
それか
The main mirror vein of the left eye ruptured
左目の主鏡静脈が断裂
that's painless
それは痛くない
More than 28 days to see a doctor
医師の診察を受けるには28日以上必要
So follow that eye
だからその瞳を追って
Entire vision is gone
視界全体が消えてしまう
that he said this in the early days
彼は初期の頃にこんなことを言っていた
at that Taipei Medical College
あの台北医科大学で
He said that with that similar treatment
彼は同じような扱いでこう言いました
Of course the spring of 2006
もちろん2006年の春
Taipei Medical University gave up
台北医科大学断念
He said there was no way to make a special trip
彼は特別な旅行をする方法はないと言いました
He asked me about the dragon bug I told him to go to Taiwan Road
ドラゴンバグについて尋ねられたので、台湾路に行くように言いました
Because at that time there were only these two hospitals
当時はこの2病院しかなかったので
You can use that avestin when you get the government's punctuality
政府の時間を守るときは、そのアベスチンを使用できます
He said that the medicine was supposed to cure liver cancer
彼はその薬は肝臓がんを治すはずだと言った
But the effect is not good
でも効果は半端ない
He said to use this to suppress this
彼はこれを抑制するためにこれを使用すると言った
Clean Tube Treatment Works Well
クリーンチューブ処理が効果的
My eye became a ruptured vein
私の目は血管が切れてしまいました
So the human body is the source of many threats
つまり人体は多くの脅威の源である
But when the threat tube increases
しかし、脅威のチューブが増加すると、
a question that blood pressure
血圧に関する質問
Soared to 63 at the highest
最高63まで上昇
I feel like throwing up all day, I can't even fight
一日中吐きそうだ、戦うこともできない
He said in the early days before
彼は以前の初期の頃にこう言った
If it doesn't work, it has to be removed.
機能しない場合は削除する必要があります
Then there is this medicine
それからこの薬があります
He hit this eye
彼はこの目に当たった
That one dose is 28,000 yuan
その1回分は28,000元です
Not covered by health insurance
健保不給負的
But the potion is not so big because the eyeballs are not dry
でも眼球は乾いていないので薬はそれほど大きくない
so measles
だから麻疹
Four people taking that one dose at the same time
4人が同時にその1回分を服用する
but after injection
でも注射後
after more than a year
1年以上経ってから
His vision is now restored
彼の視力は今では回復しています
It's that transformation image
その変身イメージです
won't distort
歪みません
But that no way is no way liquid poison
でもそんなはずはない 液体毒だ
But now it reverts every three months
しかし、今では3か月ごとに元に戻ります
that kid is normal
あの子は普通だよ
He said that the medicine man will be fine
彼は祈祷師は大丈夫だと言いました
or something later
または後で何か
Sorry, I
ごめんなさい私
I said one of you, you got the data in the invasion
私はあなた方の一人が侵略のデータを手に入れたと言いました
That Avasin just didn't talk
アヴァシンは何も話さなかった
Yeah, except for that swollen cow
そう、あの腫れた牛を除いては
It is another word that is useful in Yan Fu
これもヤンフーで役立つ言葉です
Because our eyes are an interesting organ
私たちの目は興味深い器官だから
That is to say, generally speaking, if your body says that a blood vessel is broken,
つまり、一般的に言えば、血管が壊れていると身体が判断すると、
Then the body will have regenerative blood vessels to pre-close it
そうすれば、体にはあらかじめ閉じるための再生血管が備わります。
But the eyes cannot grow blood vessels casually
でも目にはむやみに血管を伸ばすことはできません
Then your problem is that blood vessels grow out
そうすると、問題は血管が伸びることです
it affects your vision
それはあなたの視力に影響を与えます
The treatment of mentally retarded new blood vessels
精神薄弱者の新生血管の治療
Avasin is a
アヴァシンは、
In addition there are other
他にもあります
Like the Leise just mentioned, it is a very traditional medicinal bladder
先ほど述べた Leise と同様、非常に伝統的な薬用膀胱です。
photodynamic therapy
光力学療法
It is the substance that takes it with a sense of light
光の感覚で受け止める物質です
Burn it in the way of ray light
光線で燃やしてください
that's all
それで全部です
So now it means that there are two stalls of the same drug
これは、同じ薬の販売店が 2 つあることを意味します。
The curative effect is pretty good
治癒効果はかなり良い
Then you just talked about how Avasin has sequelae
それから、あなたはアヴァシンに後遺症があることについて話しました。
I don't think there will be any repercussions
何も影響はないと思います
So it should be put here
だからここに置くべきだよ
This has passed very strict human experiments.
これは非常に厳しい人体実験をパスしています。
I don't think so
私はそうは思わない
Because usually what I just mentioned means human experiments
なぜなら、私が今言ったことは通常、人体実験を意味するからです
Although there are three stages
３段階ありますが、
In fact there is a fourth stage
実は第4段階がある
Even if the first time is the FDA, he collects it at any time
FDAは初めてでもいつでも回収してくれます
Even after the drug is on the market
薬が市販されてからも
He wants to collect reports on the market at any time
彼は市場に関するレポートをいつでも収集したいと考えています
If there is any adverse reaction, he will give a warning
副作用が出たら警告してくれる
So I just drugged things like Lome Ting
それで私はロメ・ティンのようなものを薬漬けにしました
It's his after warning
それは彼の警告後のものです
Warning to the end there is no way
最後まで警告、方法はありません
His drug seems to be like this, take it off the shelf
彼の薬はこんな感じだ、棚から出しなさい
so i don't think abastin
だから私はアバスチンとは思わない
Now their problem is the tumor
今彼らの問題は腫瘍です
Metastatic tumors do not respond significantly
転移性腫瘍はあまり反応しない
Then I don't think there is any problem with the eyes
それなら目には問題ないと思います
Thank you
ありがとう
Are there any other questions?
他にご質問はありますか?
later
後で
Excuse me about the H1N1 we have in the coming year
来年の新型インフルエンザについて失礼します
Did he go through this Face 1 2 3 like this
彼はこのような顔 1 2 3 を経験しましたか
That vaccine is our own domestic vaccine
そのワクチンは当社の国産ワクチンです
i believe there is
私はあると信じています
So in the end, did he follow the Protocol of Face 1 Face 2 Face 3?
結局、彼はフェイス 1、フェイス 2、フェイス 3 のプロトコルに従ったのでしょうか?
We say his watch is over the top
私たちは彼の時計が最高だと言います
For example, there is a prescribed number of people
例えば、規定の人数がある
i am not defense
私は擁護者ではありません
man at defense vaccine factory
防衛ワクチン工場の男性
i can't tell you
言えません
And if you know today our dean or anyone else
そして今日を知っているなら、私たちの学部長か他の誰かが
but i'm not in there
でも私はそこにはいない
I'm not fit for any criticism
私はいかなる批判にも適さない
Because any criticism I make is unfair to them
なぜなら、私が行う批判は彼らにとって不公平だからです
so i have no choice
だから私には選択肢がありません
I have no data to tell you
お伝えできるデータはありません
OK
OK
Erase you just mentioned
先ほど言ったものを消してください
Geneva Jaffet
ジュネーブ・ジャフェ
It seems to be off the market in the United States
アメリカでは販売されていないようです
That's a relatively new drug now
今では比較的新しい薬です
The second generation is Tasiva
二代目はタシバ
It is a branch of EGF
EGFの支店です
You say Erase
あなたは消去と言います
Erase seems to be useful for Asians
アジア人には消去が便利そう
That's from EGF
それはEGFからです
Yes, that's EGF
そう、EGFです
it seems so
そのようです
no need to eat
食べる必要はありません
But he is relatively useless to Europeans and Americans
しかし、彼はヨーロッパ人やアメリカ人にとっては比較的役に立たない
Erase is for Long Cancer
消去はロングガン用です
They found that he was committed to a less high percentage in Europe and America
彼らは、彼がヨーロッパとアメリカでそれほど高い割合でコミットしていないことを発見しました
but in asia
でもアジアでは
is very useful
とても便利です
Sixty to seventy percent of people are polluted
国民の60～70パーセントが汚染されている
that's just because
それはただの理由です
the reaction to the medicine
薬に対する反応
but did not say
しかし言わなかった
That is to say, he generally
つまり、彼は一般的に、
Because his success rate of self-reliance rate is not so high
自立成功率があまり高くないので
He may have other alternative medications that can be substituted
代替できる他の代替薬を持っている可能性があります
You also mentioned that coach
あのコーチのことも言ってましたね
Avestan的Avestan
アヴェスタンのアヴェスタン
As far as I know it is for that Metastatic
私の知る限り、それは転移性のものです
Breast Cancer is useless
乳がんは駄目だよ
you are right
あなたが正しいです
but not for all
すべての人にとってではありませんが
All of these transfers are useless
これらの転送はすべて無駄です
Just for Breast Cancer
乳がん専用
Okay, thank you
大丈夫ありがとう
that has one
それは1つあります
these nutrients
これらの栄養素を
Nutrients
栄養素
For example like Glucosamine
例えばグルコサミンなど
In fact, many of us
実際、私たちの多くは
A while ago with Sydney Heck
しばらく前にシドニー・ヘックと
we are chatting
私たちはおしゃべりしています
He is an American expert
彼はアメリカの専門家です
He said they were liars
彼は彼らは嘘つきだと言いました
no use at all
まったく役に立たない
Because of that Glucosamine
そのグルコサミンのせいで
we should do it
私たちはそれをすべきです
Sati Glucosamine
サティグルコサミン
So the dean has been talking to me for a long time
それで学部長は長い間私に話しかけてきました
open a company
会社を開く
to turn Glucosamine into
グルコサミンを変えるには
He said that's easy, get it done
彼はそれは簡単だよ、やってみろって言った
i squeezed you
私はあなたを絞めました
let's start a company
会社を始めましょう
that's what works
それが機能するのです
Because of that Glucosamine
そのグルコサミンのせいで
That solubility is not right
その溶解度は正しくありません
After that
その後
Wisdom
知恵
But say so
でもそう言ってください
I'm not fair either
私も公平ではない
My wife wants me to eat a few pills every day
妻は私に毎日数錠食べて欲しいと思っています
so
それで
I still listen to my wife
今でも妻の言うことを聞いています
but this
しかしこれは
have some nutritious food
栄養価の高い食べ物を食べる
actually
実際
Not necessarily the one they were talking about
必ずしも彼らが話していたものとは限りません
yes and
はいそして
very cheap because
とても安いので
Glucosamine
グルコサミン
how he
彼はどうやって
he is from that
彼はそこの出身です
Shrimp shells, crab shells
エビの殻、カニの殻
people are different
人は違う
then decompose it
それからそれを分解する
So it's actually cheap
だから実は安いんです
very cheap stuff
とても安いもの
but you can see
しかし、あなたは見ることができます
a can
缶
probably both
可能都
good
良い
yes
はい
thousands of dollars is expensive
数千ドルは高価だ
but
しかし
unjustified violence
不当な暴力
Fairness should take care of it
公平性を重視すべきだ
i have two questions
質問が2つあります
Just now you said Glucosamine
今グルコサミンって言いましたね
OK then if
OK、それでは
like us
私たちのような
You added because you said it was just cartilage
ただの軟骨だと言ったから付け加えた
Cartilage is your single component
軟骨は単一の構成要素です
Is it useful to add a single thing?
何かを 1 つ追加することは役に立ちますか?
The second question is, just now you said
2番目の質問は、今あなたが言いました。
in human business
人間のビジネスにおいて
It is drug discovery
創薬です
You want a lot of SOP
たくさんのSOPが欲しい
Cleaner trade phase one phase two phase three
よりクリーンな貿易 フェーズ 1 フェーズ 2 フェーズ 3
if a drug
薬なら
it has passed in the usa
アメリカでは過ぎてしまいました
它的 phase one phase two phase three
第三のフェーズ 1 フェーズ 2 フェーズ 3
Do we have to do the same procedure in Taiwan?
台湾でも同じ手続きをしなければなりませんか？
Because of different races?
人種が違うから？
I answer your second question
2番目の質問に答えます
Usually it means this clinical trial
通常、この臨床試験を意味します
tantamount to saying
言ってるのに等しい
So this is a couple of issues
これはいくつかの問題です
very good question
とても良い質問
That is to say today a clinical trial
つまり今日は臨床試験です
it must be in
それは中にあるはずです
because if you take into account the issue of race
なぜなら、人種の問題を考慮すると、
Different races react differently to drugs
人種が異なれば薬物に対する反応も異なります
So it must be in a different area of ​​the drug
したがって、それは薬物の異なる領域にあるはずです
able to do some clinical trials
いくつかの臨床試験を行うことができる
It collects enough data
十分なデータが集まります
it can know to say
それは言うことができる
There are different reactions in different regions
地域によって反応も違う
The second is to say
2つ目は、こう言うことです
The understanding of the second consideration is that
2 番目の考慮事項の理解は次のとおりです。
In fact these protocols
実際、これらのプロトコルは
like you said
あなたが言ったように
in fact there is
実際にはあります
it has certain rules
それには一定のルールがある
that now
那現在
There are many medicines in Taiwan now
台湾には今たくさんの薬があります
Come to Taiwan to do CleanLTry
CleanLTryをするために台湾に来てください
In fact, we are follow US FDA
実際、当社は米国FDAに従っています。
the prologue
プロローグ
we think his procigil
私たちは彼のプロシギルだと思う
to his program to do
彼のプログラムにやるべきこと
So in the future these things
したがって、将来的にはこれらのこと
It is the US FDA, which will naturally pass
それは米国FDAです、当然通過します
If we say that some countries today
今日の一部の国と言ったら
like japan or other countries
日本や他の国のように
Their standards are different from FDA
彼らの基準はFDAとは異なります
Then he passed the experiment in Japan
そして彼は日本での実験に合格した
He's going to America to do it all over again
彼はもう一度やり直すためにアメリカへ行くつもりだ
Because he adopts different standards
彼は異なる基準を採用しているため
So it turns into whether you want to be in line with international standards
つまり、国際標準に準拠するかどうかが重要になります
just like sync
同期のように
That's relatively easy
その方が面倒が少ない
Then we follow FDA standards to do
次に、FDA の基準に従い、次のことを行います。
OK
OK
Then your first question was
それからあなたの最初の質問は
Say you Google
グーグルって言ってください
Yeah
うん
can't that be
そんなことはありえない
No
いいえ
Because of the Google gas you just mentioned
先ほどおっしゃった Google ガスのせいで
The other one is Google gas
もう 1 つは Google ガスです
of our body
私たちの体の
or Google gas
またはGoogleガス
on google
Googleで
He can sell people very expensive
彼は人を非常に高く売ることができる
is worth not staying pathological
病的なままではいけない
So can't hope for a long time that I can start a company
だから会社を立ち上げることは長い間望めない
I also hope that
私もそう願っています
Ask Professor Lin
リン教授に聞く
the one you just mentioned
あなたが今言ったもの
Astilin is extracted from that Liushi
アスティリンはそのリュウシから抽出される
right
右
and that
そしてそれ
That Purple Mountain Lip of the Pacific Purple Mountain
太平洋紫山脈の紫山唇
then ask you
それからあなたに尋ねてください
that this
これは
Medicines like this belong to natural medicine
このような薬は自然医学に属します
still belongs to western medicine
まだ西洋医学に属する
Another problem is
もう一つの問題は
About your anti-cancer and another kind of that
あなたの抗がん剤とその他の抗がん剤について
Anti-cancer drugs are extracted from customs
抗がん剤は税関から抜き取られる
Then do you think this anti-cancer drug is effective?
では、この抗がん剤は効果があると思いますか？
what you just said
あなたが今言ったこと
The effects of Asti and Aretha
アスティとアレサの効果
which one is better
どちらがいいですか
Thanks
ありがとう
The second question is because of that
2番目の質問はそのためです
Because many medicines have different injection chambers
多くの薬には異なる注入チャンバーがあるため
have a name or we don't
名前があるかないか
i don't know what it is
それが何なのか分かりません
so i can't answer you
だから私はあなたに答えることができません
I have no way to answer the second question just mentioned
先ほど述べた 2 番目の質問に答える方法がありません
the first one
最初の1つ
you speak so-so
あなたはまあまあ話す
We just talked about paper mountain lip or aspirin
先ほどペーパー・マウンテン・リップやアスピリンについて話しました。
It is from the natural temperature
自然の温度によるものです
But you can't say I'm today because it works
でも、それがうまくいったから今日だとは言えません
as people said before
前に人々が言っ​​たように
Anti-cow feeling should be made from star anise
反牛感情はスターアニスから作られるべきです
just ran to buy star anise
スターアニスを買いに走ったところです
logic doesn't work like this
このようにロジックは機能しません
Why?
なぜ？
because you go straight to
あなたはまっすぐに行くから
I induce you to give birth
出産を勧めます
you eat directly
直接食べます
Assuming there are vegetarian skins to eat
ベジタリアン向けの皮があると仮定すると、
The problem is that it has different ingredients in it
問題は、含まれている成分が異なることです
you eat
あなたは食べる
you eat these ingredients
あなたはこれらの食材を食べます
In addition, we usually
さらに、私たちは通常、
These studies usually brittle these things out
これらの研究は通常、これらのことをもろくします
and you know the amount
そしてあなたはその金額を知っています
If you directly from the natural temperature tax
自然温度税から直接いただく場合
when your medicine
あなたの薬はいつ
that dose is very low
その線量は非常に低いです
Then you have different other ingredients
それから、他の材料もいろいろあります
this is very complicated
これはとても複雑です
So this is where Chinese medicine differs from Western medicine.
ここが中国医学が西洋医学と違うところです。
words of Chinese medicine
中医学の言葉
it is to emphasize this
これを強調するためです
The effect of combining different ingredients
さまざまな成分を組み合わせる効果
That's Western medicine, it's
それが西洋医学ですよ
it's clear
それは明らかだ
because you look at the single ingredient
単一の成分に注目するからです
but it tells you
しかしそれはあなたに伝えます
I want to experiment with cells
細胞の実験をしてみたい
experiments with animals
動物を使った実験
experiments with humans
人間を使った実験
These currencies also have my ability
これらの通貨にも私の能力があります
can make you eat
あなたに食べさせることができます
This logic is different from philosophy
この論理は哲学とは異なります
but i mean
しかし、私が言いたいのは
He is extracted like this
彼はこのように抽出されます
It also belongs to the natural medicine medicine
自然医学にも属します
or western medicine
西洋医学とか
Western medicine
西洋医学
Okay, thank you
大丈夫ありがとう
Yes, he is already a single compound
はい、彼はすでに単一の化合物です
do it with a single compound
単一の化合物でそれを行う
This continues some of the clinical careers above
これは上記の臨床キャリアの一部を継続します
So he is already a thing of western medicine
つまり、彼はすでに西洋医学のものです
Western medicine
西洋医学
right
右
And the molecule will be modified again like just now
そして先ほどのようにまた分子が改変されていきます
Like that Hoffmann just now for his neighborhood
まるで近所のためだけのあのホフマンのように
he did some chemistry with him
彼は彼と化学反応を起こした
he still modified
彼はまだ修正した
what do you think
どう思いますか
you, let me add
あなた、付け加えさせてください
The wash you just asked about
先ほどご質問いただいた洗濯について
That's Tob Teigen
それはトブ・テイゲンです
Temple Teigen kind of thing
寺帝源的なもの
Then his mechanism of action is different from that of Zishanchun.
したがって、彼の作用機序は紫山春とは異なります。
Texel acts on the microtubules he just mentioned
テクセルは彼が先ほど述べた微小管に作用します
The one from Jubilant
ジュビラントのもの
that synthetic
その合成
that wash this
これを洗うのは
is an efficiency that acts on the action of DNA
DNAの作用に作用する効率です
These two are not the same
これら 2 つは同じではありません
He is in our Converse land
彼は私たちのコンバースの国にいる
In Taiwan, it is currently the health insurance index
台湾では現在、健康保険指数となっています。
used for a while
しばらく使用した
no
いいえ
it's the large intestine
それは大腸です
Fatty bowel cancer
大腸脂腸癌
Feel sorry
気の毒だと思う
It is used in colorectal adipose bowel cancer
結腸直腸脂肪腸がんに使用されます
health care index
ヘルスケアインデックス
Thanks
ありがとう
Professor Lin, ask me
リン先生、聞いてください
two questions
2つの質問
first question
最初の質問
Can Painkillers Harm Your Liver?
鎮痛剤は肝臓に害を及ぼす可能性がありますか?
second question
2番目の質問
My mother has been suffering from severe gout recently
私の母は最近重度の痛風に苦しんでいます
I took her to see a doctor at Chenda Hospital
私は彼女をチェンダ病院の医者に連れて行きました
As a result, the doctor
その結果、医師は、
just opened that rib lip
肋骨を開いたばかりです
I freaked out when I saw the rib lip
リブリップ見てびっくりした
And open four
そして4つ開ける
So eat four at a time
だから一度に4つ食べる
Each tablet is about 5mg
1錠あたり約5mg
then i want to ask
それから聞きたいです
We are generally not on the rib lip
通常、肋骨の上にはいません
have a bad impression
悪い印象を持つ
Said to eat too much
食べ過ぎと言われました
not good for health
健康に良くない
can you explain
説明できますか
I'm still emphasizing
まだ強調してるよ
not a doctor
医者ではありません
Not a doctor at National Taiwan University Hospital
国立台湾大学病院の医師ではありません
I'm just a little researcher
私はほんの小さな研究者です
so i didn't really didn't
だから私は本当にしませんでした
and i didn't see your mother
そしてあなたのお母さんに会いませんでした
What kind of symptoms does she have?
彼女にはどんな症状があるのでしょうか？
I really can't make this diagnosis
本当にこの診断はできない
It's really something that has no limited manpower.
それは本当に人的資源に制限がないものです。
there is no way
道はない
I'm just asking about steroids
ステロイドについて質問です
tell you
教えてください
The problem is Steroid it has a different effect
問題はステロイドです、それは別の効果を持っています
And it often makes some
そして、それはしばしばいくつかのものを作ります
adjustment
調整
So you usually have to be very careful when using
したがって、通常、使用するときは非常に注意する必要があります
then i guess maybe
それから、おそらく
I don't know if it's because of your mother
お母さんのせいなのかは分かりませんが、
have specific symptoms
特定の症状がある
so the doctor has
それで医者は
There will also be such a class assessment achievement
こんな授業評価実績もあります
I think you should be direct
直接言うべきだと思う
do one with the doctor
医者と相談してください
to communicate face to face
対面でコミュニケーションをとる
this is better
これの方が良い
I can't give you a split opinion
意見が分かれることはありません
what was your first question
最初の質問は何でしたか
Can Painkillers Hurt Your Liver?
鎮痛剤は肝臓を傷つける可能性がありますか?
That painkiller hurts the liver
その鎮痛剤は肝臓を痛める
This is on the side of the Puna phlegm
これはプナ痰の側面です
There is an explanation
説明があります
If you have read relevant information
関連情報を読んだ場合
But usually
でも、普段は
Propula
発疹
His scar basically has two prerequisites
彼の傷跡には基本的に 2 つの前提条件があります
the first one you want to overdose
最初に過剰摂取したいもの
Because generally speaking, the dosage of Pranaden
一般的に言えば、プラナデンの投与量は
If as far as I know it is 500mg
私の知る限りでは500mgです
then you
次にあなた
Usually the dosage can reach 67 times
通常、投与量は67倍に達することがあります
He's just starting to have scars
彼には傷跡が残り始めたばかりだ
So two prerequisites
したがって、2つの前提条件
one is that you want to overdose
1つは過剰摂取したいということです
Basically if you follow your prescription for a day
基本的には処方箋を1日守っていれば
you can never overdose
過剰摂取は決してできません
The second is that you have to cooperate with alcohol
2つ目は、お酒には協力しなければならないということです。
it means you drink
それはあなたが飲むことを意味します
And then eat Proden
そしてプロデンを食べる
that will scar
それは傷跡を残すでしょう
But generally speaking, the effect of Proton
しかし、一般的に言えば、プロトンの効果は、
Usually low value
通常は低い値
unless you have these two conditions
この2つの条件が揃っていない限り、
He gets scars when he cooperates
協力すると傷が付く
i want to return to
に戻りたいです
The period film of our nutrition
私たちの栄養の時代劇
That is to say, health medicine does not
つまり、健康医学はそうではありません
Then my question is
それから私の質問は
such as sleeping pills
睡眠薬などの
or political economy
政治経済とか
generally
一般
when the doctor prescribed
医師が処方したとき
patients usually
病人通常
I still wish I could not eat it.
今でも食べなければよかったと思っています。
for fear of being dependent
依存してしまうのが怖いから
Then they'd like to be able to use another way
その後、別の方法を使用できるようにしたいと考えています
Also all I know is
また、私が知っているのは
A recent friend, Mr. He
最近の友達、何さん
Because I moved for a long time after taking the medicine
薬を服用してから長期間移動したため
Finally sent to the emergency room
ついに救急病院に送られました
But the one in therapy
しかし、治療中の人は
The doctor in the emergency room gave him another shot
救急医は彼にもう一度投与した
He turned into a vegetable
彼は野菜になってしまった
So now I take the medicine
それで今薬を飲みます
Generally, I still hope that I can not take medicine without taking medicine.
一般的には、薬を飲まなければ薬が飲めないことを今でも願っています。
I have the same opinion
私も同じ意見です
because I want
私が欲しいから
Sometimes the Central Plains Institute is under great pressure
セントラルプレーンズ研究所は時々大きなプレッシャーにさらされることがあります
Can't sleep or keep sleeping
眠れない、または眠り続ける
you are stressed
あなたはストレスを感じています
So my own feeling is that later I relied on exercise
だから私自身の感覚では、その後は運動に頼るようになった
because it means you can't sleep
それは眠れないということだから
Maybe you have too much energy
エネルギーがありすぎるのかもしれません
Later, I developed the habit of exercising myself
その後、自分で運動する習慣がつきました
10:00 p.m. Natural men want to sleep
午後10時 天然男は寝たい
that's the best way
それが最善の方法です
So my own experience is that
それで、私自身の経験としては、
of course i will agree with you
もちろん同意します
Unless if you really need to use
本当に使用する必要がある場合を除き、
I would suggest you to see a doctor for an IQ test
医師の診察を受けてIQテストを受けることをお勧めします
Now Taiwan's problem is
今台湾の問題は
Because health care products you know you need to know
ヘルスケア製品については知っておく必要があるため
you go to the doctor
あなたは医者に行きます
Of course the hospital will give you 3 minutes and 5 minutes
もちろん病院は3分と5分を与えます
about to be kicked out
追い出されそうになる
So if you have an IQ
だからIQがあるなら
subject doctor
担当医師
talk to him well
彼とよく話してください
Because usually doctors start firing
たいてい医師は発砲し始めるから
basically knowing your medical history
基本的に自分の病歴を知ること
Or do you have any of these techniques for taking medicine
または、薬を服用するためのこれらのテクニックを持っていますか
or even have an allergy
あるいはアレルギーを持っている場合もあります
Like academician Zhong, a member of our hospital
私たちの病院の会員である鍾学者のように
His allergy to that allergy drug
そのアレルギー薬に対する彼のアレルギー
and good research
そして良い研究
You need to understand these things
これらのことを理解する必要があります
Only then can the medicine that really suits you be dismissed
そうして初めて、本当に自分に合った薬を無視することができます
right now we just talked about
今ちょうど話したところです
personalized therapy
個別化された療法
personalized medicine
個別化医療
is the most important
才最重要
The health insurance system, I suggest
健康保険制度をお勧めします
You should find a family doctor you can trust
信頼できるかかりつけ医を見つけるべきです
He can do some better counseling
彼はもう少し良いカウンセリングができるだろう
In this case, you will not use enough drugs
この場合、十分な量の薬を使用することはできません
i don't think it will go wrong
うまくいかないとは思わない
Then he has someone, you are after
それなら彼には誰かがいる、あなたが追いかけている
you fade
あなたは消えます
i have an idea that you are
私はあなたがそうだという考えを持っています
What is the so-called voter medicine?
いわゆる有権者の薬とは何ですか？
It means that his patent has passed zero, so it can be opened
それは彼の特許がゼロを超えたので公開できることを意味します
Drugs that everyone can produce
誰でも作れる薬を作る
Not wrong, because of the so-called professional, because he spent a lot of time opening the pharmaceutical factory
いわゆるプロフェッショナルなので、製薬工場の開設に多くの時間を費やしたので、間違いではありません
So usually the patent protection period is about 12 to 15 years.
したがって、通常、特許の保護期間は約 12 ～ 15 年です。
you start
あなたが始めます
After registering this patent, you can get a reward and then sell it
この特許を登録すると、報酬を受け取り、販売することができます
So sometimes after too long a delay, he really
それで時々、あまりにも長い遅れの後、彼は本当に
Can sell the whole world alone only you can sell
全世界を一人で売ることができるのはあなただけです
that may not be a few years
それは数年ではないかもしれない
so he gave you a while
それで彼はあなたに少し時間を与えました
But a patent is about to fall
でも特許が落ちそう
This patent has passed
この特許は合格しました
All pharmaceutical factories are put into production
すべての製薬工場が生産を開始
So generally speaking, it should be cheaper to learn folk medicine
したがって、一般的に言えば、民間療法を学ぶ方が安くなるはずです
Because everyone can produce
誰でも生み出せるから
It should be relatively simple to compete in the next grid
次のグリッドで競争するのは比較的簡単なはずです
So Suscanol is
それでサスカノールは
Is it the unobtainable scholar medicine?
それは入手不可能な学者の医学ですか？
I know it's Panodol
パノドールだということは知っています
I don't know if there are other
他にもあるかどうかはわかりません
Shoppers
買い物客
Astamino Fan
アスタミノファン
this medicine you
この薬はあなたに
I have a cold recently
最近風邪をひいています
so i go buy this
だからこれを買いに行きます
The blessing hat is to make up for it
祝福の帽子はそれを補うものです
You open that medicine list and look at it
その薬リストを開いて見てください
at least twenty names
少なくとも20の名前
so
それで
Just say a name, it doesn't have to be
名前を言ってください、そうである必要はありません
That's because the blessing hat has
それは、祝福の帽子があるからです。
neutralize symptoms
症状を中和する
so it curbs your runny nose
それで鼻水を抑えます
Stop knocking
ノックをやめる
It's got a bunch so it's got a lot of medicine in it
たくさん入っているので薬もたっぷり入っています
the same medicine
同じ薬
that
それか
that drug
その薬
its name
その名前
There are twenty-three kinds of names because different names came out.
いろいろな名前が出てきたので二十三種類あります。
So everyone is probably saying the same thing
だからみんな同じこと言ってるかもしれない
have a different name
違う名前を持っています
OK, is there anything else?
OK、他に何かありますか？
the student
学生
here then please
ここでお願いします
hello i ask two
こんにちは、2人に聞きます
I ask two questions
2つ質問します
maybe my question is a bit stupid
私の質問は少し愚かかもしれません
that is
あれは
Why are there so many drugs
なぜこんなに薬が多いのか
It is metabolized to go out in the end
最後に出ていくために代謝される
Then when it biochemically reacts
そして生化学的に反応すると
No, structural changes cannot happen immediately
いいえ、構造変化はすぐには起こりません
first question
最初の質問
then the second question
それから2番目の質問
can i go over that spring part again
もう一度そのスプリング部分を見直してもいいですか
that is
あれは
Because I have researched that Reynolds backsong
レイノルズのバックソングを調べたから
then i should say
それなら私は言うべきです
that
それか
Because I went to study that
それを勉強しに行ったから
the capital compound
首都の複合施設
solid compound
固体化合物
because it has slow
遅いから
then i want to ask
それから聞きたいです
Can you say Spring again
また春って言えますか
how to prove
証明する方法
It is a non-ethnic compound
非民族複合体です
But it can also achieve
しかし、それは達成することもできます
Anti-addiction effect
抗依存症効果
first question
最初の質問
drug metabolism
薬物代謝
usual practice
いつもの練習
he didn't
彼はしませんでした
take a medicine
薬を服用する
Then from the original molecule
次に、元の分子から
run out like this
このように使い果たされる
absolutely impossible
絶対に無理
usually especially some
通常、特に一部の
water-based drugs
水ベースの薬
Usually above he will do some oxidation
通常、彼はある程度の酸化を行います
usually
いつもの
The approach is that he wants to be on top of this drug
アプローチは、彼がこの薬物を最大限に活用したいということです
do the same similar
同じようなことをする
he is going to track
彼は追跡するつもりです
e.g. in blood
例：血液中
he wants to clarify
彼ははっきりさせたいと思っています
Then purify
それから浄化してください
to identify what he has become
彼がどうなったのかを特定するために
what kind of biochemical reaction
どのような生化学反応ですか
that is in
それは中にあります
Pri-Kin-Yo-Three
プリキンヨースリー
In fact he was
実際、彼はそうでした
money
金ーよーＴ理
FaceOne, he is going to do these studies now
FaceOne、彼はこれからこれらの研究を行うつもりです
this must be done
これはやらなければいけない
so impossible
とても不可能
most will not
ほとんどはそうではありません
Running out like this
このまま走り出す
absolutely not
絶対違う
the second
二番目
you talk about lace dragon
あなたはレースドラゴンについて話します
because you signed a lot
たくさんサインしてくれたから
Chinese translated name
中国語に翻訳された名前
we have no way
私たちには方法がありません
so we can
だから私たちはできる
Let's talk about this in private, okay?
このことについてはプライベートで話しましょう、いいですか？
if you need me
もしあなたが私を必要とするなら
I will meet in Aspen
アスペンで会いましょう
to explain
説明する
otherwise i
そうでなければ私は
he was everyone's time
彼はみんなの時間だった
We can talk to you directly
直接お話しさせていただきます
OK
OK
if there are no other questions
他に質問がなければ
do we thank you again
もう一度感謝しますか
pay attention to what we say
私たちの言うことに注意してください
Thanks
ありがとう